The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
The result of pride, huh?
Those guys don't know about themselves.
There is nothing more terrifying than obliviousness.
However...
Do you have a plan?
Please leave it to me, Superbia...
Avaritia-sama.
As you wish.
The Time of Disasters
Kakeru-kun...
Ah, sorry. I fell asleep.
Want some water?
I'm all right.
Take a good rest today.
You're tired, right?
I have to call my mom...
I already have.
You don't have to worry.
Thank you.
As long as we're in this world, we're fine.
Just relax and sleep.
I'll protect you.
I'll be the one to protect you, Kakeru-kun.
Silly, I'll be the one to protect you.
But... thank you.
Here.
Okay.
Where's Yukiko?
Ah, she's sleeping in her room.
It seems she's lost her stamina.
Yuka is sleeping.
Let's all just take a break today.
It'll be dangerous to go into the Crimson Night separately.
Yes
Sorry, but can you pour some tea?
We sure can use that power.
I'm talking about Yuka.
We may be able to win if we use that power.
Well, that means we'll also be powerless.
To win, huh.
Takahisa.
What is it that we should win against?
What should we do to end this?
Be swallowed by the Crimson Night...
Put an end to the black knights...
All we do is fight,
in order to protect ourselves.
It can't be helped, right?
They keep attacking us.
What does "fragment" mean?
Other than the six of us being students, we have nothing in common.
What is the "sin" that the black knights speak of?
We fight 'cause they attack us.
The only thing to do in a fight is win.
That's all there is.
Where are you going?
I'm being distressed.
This isn't like me.
"The one who awoke the demon is you."
Did you write that?
What in the world are you?
Are you an ally?
Just please don't hurt Yuka.
I don't care what happens to me, but...
Not Yuka.
Please.
I have no
memory of the past
Hey.
Takahisa-senpai...
Good morning.
Oh, morning.
How's Yuka?
She's asleep.
What are you doing?
I'm checking our barrier.
Barrier?
It's surrounding the estate.
If a demon comes, it'll react.
Demon?
What's that about?
Isn't this world safe?
You can't be too careful.
Can you sense it with your powers as an Onmyouji?
Senpai?
Kakeru, come with me for a bit.
All right.
To Kakeru?
Yes.
I...
Something like that isn't something to worry about.
But...
That was during a fight. You couldn't help it.
Anyways, it's his fault for going around all over the place.
If you keep worrying about something like that,
you won't be able to win a battle you would have won.
First comes winning. Living.
If he died there, that means it would've been his fate.
That's... sad.
Huh?
If that happened, he'd be all alone.
What are you talking about?
Isn't that how you've been living up 'til now?
You've survived, right?
That's because I can't die.
I've seen many deaths.
Even people I loved very much.
They've died in front of my eyes.
I've had enough.
I don't want anymore.
It breaks my heart...
...and...
...another side of me surfaces...
Yukiko...
I won't make any more friends.
I'm fine alone.
That's what I thought.
That it was enough.
But...
For friends and for tomorrow.
I hate the crimson night, but...
Thanks to that, I've made more friends.
I met people who accept who I am.
Takahisa-senpai...
I met you, too.
I love everyone.
I really, really love everyone.
That's why... That's why I didn't want to hurt anyone!
You're not alone anymore, Takahisa-senpai.
You're being protected, right?
I don't remember ever being...
That's wrong.
There is Saeko-sensei.
She's... not like that.
She used both Eastern and Western skills.
There's a forbidden incantation called the "Gehou."
Seventy years ago...
The Onmyouji that was expelled for using that "Gehou"...
Her name was Kusakabe Misao.
She's a woman who can cast high-level incantations.
While I was investigating her, I found myself looking up to her.
A strong, noble woman...
My feelings for her still haven't changed.
Why are you telling me this?
The Black Knight called Superbia...
She is Kusakabe Misao.
Kakeru-kun...
Why she's in the Crimson Night and why she's a Black Knight, I don't know.
But she is, without a doubt, Misao.
That's... That's just weird.
The person called Misao was from seventy years ago, right?
Isn't she already dead?
There is no concept of time in the Crimson Night.
You should have noticed this as well.
After crossing over, no matter how much time passes, when you return it's the same instant as when you left.
In the world where the stream of time is halted, Misao Kusakabe...
...has continued to live to seventy years.
And became a Black Knight.
There was punishment.
Punishment?
This is the mark of one that has used "Gehou".
Right before the beginning of the Crimson Night,
I had been struck by a mysterious wind while I was divining a fortune and was branded.
The person I admire now stands before me as an enemy.
Not only that, it is a fact that the difference in power was proven last night.
Right now, she's not an opponent I can possibly face.
Senpai, what are you...
Senpai?
Drink my blood.
Kakeru, I'll entrust the powers of Kusakabe to you.
Kakeru-kun...
Here.
This is for you.
This is also for Yuka.
Drink it.
Though I have been reduced to a witch of time, I still have a heart.
This burning feeling I have for you...
This love without falsehood...
Ah, I promise.
This world that you despised so much...
This world that stole your future...
I will definitely... definitely erase it.
I love you...
Verard.
The weather is too good.
Takahisa!
Crud!
Come here!
Ouch, ouch, ouch!
Hey, stop it! Hey!
No excuses!
Infirmary
It sure has the best aroma when it's just opened.
Am I gonna hear your lecture again here?
Oh, so you came prepared for lectures. Good.
I'm going.
Where were you last night?
Over at a friend's place.
Friend? Really now?
It's not like I have to report it to you.
What are you talking about?
If you had any issues, the person responsible would be me.
Oh, I see. It's that girl.
Huh?
The petite and cute girl with glasses.
Oh, I see, I see. That's what it's about.
Then that's fine. You can go.
Hold on! It's not like that!
That's youth for ya...
Listen to me!
It's been seven years since I've picked you up.
Now that it's passed, it sure seems fast.
Don't say things like "picked up."
I'm not an object.
Energy-to-Go
What?
Nothing.
Well, I guess I'll go to class and sleep.
Oh, that's right. Come by after school.
Huh?
It's payday, so I'll treat you to some grilled meat.
Grilled meat?
Sure.
Then just sleep a bit.
Your stomach will hurt if you eat grilled meat after staying up all night.
Eh?
That guy...
Some die in the morning; others are born in the evening.
Alive: they are like those bubbles floating on the water.
Nor is it clear to me, as people are born and die, where they are coming from and where they are going.
Hey, what do you think's happened to Yuka and Kakeru-kun?
Nor why, being so ephemeral in this world, they take such pains to make their houses pleasing to the eye.
What are you doing?
It's a flying love letter.
Huh?
Shiori-chan. Please accept this!
The master and the dwelling are competing in their transience.
A love air mail. From: Tadashi-kun.
Both will perish from this world like the morning glory that blooms in the morning dew.
Shot down.
Noooooo~!
Teruya! You got a problem?
Listen to this, Sensei!
My love-love air mail was just...
Idiot! We're still in class!
Huh? We were?
What an idiot.
Sheesh.
Sensei.
Yes? What is it, Momono?
I'm feeling a little sick, so I'm going to go to the infirmary.
I see. Are you all right on your own?
Yes.
Sensei, I'll go on a date with Shiori-chan!
I mean, I'll accompany Shiori-chan!
I'll pass.
Huh?
Just die.
They've moved?
Then I guess this means that I can't ignore this anymore.
All right, that's some good movement.
My body feels light. I can also see her movements clearly.
From the side, huh?
Senpai!
I'm all right.
I'm sorry. I just...
No, that was superb.
Don't forget what just happened.
Yes.
Yuka!
I was watching.
You were amazing.
Ah, well. It's all thanks to her.
It seems I've become stronger.
Here.
Y-Yes...
Thank you.
Yuka?
Hey, Yuka!?
Now I'm just like Kakeru-kun.
You were watching?
Yeah.
Yuka...
I ended up talking to Satchii...
Um... Sorry about before.
You were trying to cheer me up, right?
And even so, I was...
Sorry.
Here.
Drink it.
Thank you very much!
And also...
Huh?
Saeko-sensei is... Well, I can't really put it it into words...
Oh, that?
We actually take the people close to us for granted more than we think.
I'm no different.
I only figured it out after they were gone.
The people who were always there for and with me had suddenly disappeared.
It felt like a wide hole had opened up inside of me.
At that time, I realized,
"I had been supported."
"I had been protected."
Drink it.
Yes. Thanks for the drink.
Thank you.
I have to tell you...
I may have not noticed.
Takahisa-senpai...
Have you gone, too?
You've had it pretty bad, huh?
But it's all right.
'Cause right now, you're in front of me.
Right?
You sure are petite.
You've been fighting so hard, despite your size.
Saeko, if you hadn't picked me up, I wouldn't be here.
No, I probably wouldn't even be alive.
Thank you.
Once the Crimson Night ends, let's go touring somewhere.
You, me, and Yukiko.
I bet it'll be fun.
I'm gonna go search a bit.
Yes.
Geez, that Yukiko.
I told her so many times not to move around so much.
If she comes back, be sure to let me know.
I understand.
Come on. Let's go.
See you later!
What's wrong, Kakeru-kun?
Oh, nothing. Let's go in.
Yeah.
Did something happen with Kakeru?
You seem to resemble his older sister.
He probably can't communicate with you too well.
If I can help, just let me know.
I'll talk with Kakeru.
I'll leave this here.
Sure.
What's up with the sudden cleaning frenzy?
We're freeloaders here. We should at least clean up.
Now this is the Yuka I'm used to.
What's wrong?
That...
Oh, a gecko.
I'm scared of lizards...
Don't worry. It's not poisonous, and it protects the house.
It won't attack or anything.
But if it bothers you, I'll catch it and bring it out...
Kakeru-kun, you're warm...
Yuka...
It'd be nice if it were always just you and me.
I wonder if they found Yukiko-chan.
I don't know!
Yuka?
I don't want to hear things like that!
What was that?
It's the second floor.
I'm gonna go check it out.
No, I want to go with you!
If anything were to happen to you, I'd use my powers and...
You can't do that, Yuka.
Eh?
I don't want you to use your power.
Why? Do you hate me now?
What are you talking about? It's not like that.
When you use your powers, you become tired, right?
I don't want you to suffer any more.
I'm gonna go check the second floor. Stay here, okay?
All right, I got it.
Once the Crimson Night ends, everything will be back to normal.
If it ever does...
If that happens, Yuka will surely...
So that's what happened. There's a draft going through here.
I've been waiting, Master of the Aeon's Eye.
Shiori...-san?
What are you doing!? Who are you?
I've been sent by the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
I am Shiori Momono. My true name is Summoner Ursula.
Why me?
That is because you have awoken the demon.
It'd be nice if the Crimson Night doesn't come today.
That's right.
But is it really all right for me to come with you?
It's all right. Saeko's payday is everyone's payday.
That's mean! But I'll come along since you said so.
Yeah! Eat up, eat up! Eat it all up!
It's been so long since I've had grilled meat!
Hey, Saeko!
Let's go.
S-Sae...ko...
Next time: The Broken Bonds
And thus, the two of them lived happily ever after.
Next Time
The Broken Bonds