The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
A black moon...
How?
Why?
What is going on?
I don't know.
However, I do know that this is certainly not a good omen.
Lonely Pride
From now on, whenever we are sent into the Crimson Night...
...let's gather together at this school.
Yes.
Also, that girl that I said I'd introduce to you...
...still doesn't feel up to it.
Eh? She doesn't want to meet us?
I think that we'd be more composed if we were together, though.
Everyone has personal issues.
Just wait a bit longer.
I understand.
See you later.
Ah, Kusakabe-senpai.
What is it, Satsuki-kun?
Um...
I have something to discuss with you later.
I see. Well then, come to my classroom at lunch break.
Okay.
What did you mean by "something to discuss", Kakeru-kun?
It's nothing.
Come on, class is gonna start soon.
Kakeru-kun...
The person who woke up the demon...
... is you.
A demon...
... was it?
So then "you" is...
It really is me.
If so, then...
...it's my fault that Yuka and everyone else have been dragged into the Crimson Night.
All because of me...
For the next problem... Satsuki-kun.
Satsuki-kun?
Kakeru-kun... Kakeru-kun!
Huh?
Ah!
S-Sorry.
We're in the middle of class, you know.
Don't be daydreaming now.
Sorry...
Kakeru-kun!
Not enough sleep?
You must've been doing something staying up late, eh?
Pervert!
Kaori-san!
Hitting people with textbooks means failing this grade!
Sensei, please throw this noisy piece of trash away quickly.
You're so mean! What do you mean by "trash"?!
Okay, okay. That's enough.
You can play around more during recess.
Powers?
Yes.
I want to awaken them.
Powers that are supposedly dormant inside of me.
What do you want me to do?
Please teach me how to fight!
If these dormant powers are meant for fighting...
... then they might awaken if I fight.
No, they should awaken!
That'd be nice.
I understand your feeling to protect Yuka Minase.
However, haste tends to bring about mistakes.
You can't become an expert overnight.
I know that.
Even so, I want to do it.
No... It's something I must do.
Because of me...
Please, Kusakabe-senpai.
Please teach me how to use a sword!
I refuse.
Senpai, please wait!
Hey, let's eat over there!
Let's go!
I've found you, Yuka-san!
Y-Yukiko-chan...
Ah! That looks delicious!
May I have just a bite?
Avocado and shrimp, huh?
This is really good!
Yummy, yummy!
Thank you for the food!
You said just a bite...
Eh? Ah, I'm sorry!
It was so tasty that I just ate it all.
Thank you.
Huh? For what?
Isn't this where you get mad at me for eating it all...?
Ah! Could it be that you've poisoned it!?
That's not it.
I just felt better after seeing your smile.
That's why... thank you.
Ah! So that's what you were going on about.
Well then, I'll smile some more for you.
This isn't good. There's no point in reading this bogus.
Is he an acquaintance of yours, Yukiko-chan?
Eh? Uh... kind of...
Could it be...
... someone you like?
Ehh?
That's wrong!
Geez, what are you saying, Yuka-san?
So that's not it... I'm sorry.
That person...
I don't know how to put this, but...
He's the same.
That person is... also suffering.
Yukiko-chan...
Yuka-san, I didn't think so before but you actually have some pretty nice breasts!
They feel so good!
H-Hold on, Yukiko-chan-
It's so calming~
I saw that.
Saw what?
She's such a cheery and cute girl.
If you're interested...
It's not like that.
If you've got something to say, then say it.
Keeping silent and having regrets isn't good for your body.
You just lack the finesse.
All right! Shiori-chan, how's this?
It seems like there is something wrong with your head.
Eh?
That is a complete set.
Why is the fifth book beside the first?
Eh? Ah, you're right.
The numbers are not just for display, you know.
Please fix it.
What's going on?
Shiori-chan has become the librarian,
so Tadashi said he'd help out and this is how things ended up.
So that's how it is.
All right.
Okay, now it's perfect.
On second thought, let's move that whole set down one shelf.
Please do it swiftly.
Fine...
Tadashi, good luck.
Kakeru-kun...
Senpai...
Misuzu Kusakabe, huh?
The Kusakabe household has always protected the country and people,
fulfilling its role as an Onmyouji clan.
That's why I've never questioned becoming an Onmyouji.
Furthermore, if I were to become one, I wished to be strong.
It's a red seal.
A red seal?
I hold all five treasured swords of the Kusakabe lineage.
These demon swords are quite powerful, so I usually have them sealed,
but when the need arises, I summon them.
Kogarasu Maru Amakuni,
The "Kogarasu Maru" is a double bladed sword similar to both the Chinese straight sword and Japanese tachi, created by Amakuni, a legendary blacksmith considered the father of the Japanese katana.
Kashagiri Hiromitsu,
This sword was rumored to have cut a kasha (burning wagon) a demon used to steal dead bodies in half.
Kannagiri Nagamitsu,
This sword was rumored to have cut a demon in disguise as a carpenter in half along with the kanna (carpenter's plane) it was carrying.
Tachibana Dousetsu Raikiri,
Tachibana Dousetsu is a samurai rumored to have sliced a lightning bolt in half with his sword, Raikiri, the "lightning blade."
and finally...
Doujigiri Yatsuna.
This sword was rumored to have cut off the head of the demon Shuten Douji.
The Kusakabe house, being an Onmyouji clan, was required to have powerful heirs obtain the treasured swords,
so it had members of the bloodline fight with real swords, and gave one katana to each victor.
For there to be all five katanas here...
So you won all of them, right? Incredible...
Originally, in order to prevent the concentration of all the power at one point,
there's an unspoken agreement that one person should only get one sword.
Since they were all legitimate fights, though, it can't be helped.
So because of that, I had to leave my hometown.
Your hometown?
Then this house is...?
It's my mother's villa.
Because my life is being sought after by everyone in the main family,
I moved away from my family and have lived here alone.
They are after your life?
Why is that?
You got your katanas through legitimate fights, right?
Kusakabe is a distinguished family.
As a distinguished family, honor is of utmost importance.
For someone young, and also a woman,
to take all of the treasured swords isn't entertaining to my senpais.
Besides, in my last battle, I...
I'll keep my story at that.
Now, let's begin.
Yes!
It's heavier than you thought, right?
Yes...
Try it out.
Yes!
One more time.
So that's how it is.
You and Kakeru Satsuki were both raised in an institution, huh?
Yes.
Thank goodness.
Hm?
You can't see a black moon at night.
Oh...
How is Kakeru-kun?
He has no talent with the sword.
Still... it's better than him doing nothing.
Will Kakeru-kun's power awaken?
If he's lucky...
...is my answer for now.
Your last match...
You started talking about it, then stopped halfway.
What happened?
You stopped talking because you didn't want to talk about it, right?
I'm sorry.
I cut down my father.
In the fight for the last treasured sword, Doujigiri Yasutsuna...
I cut down Toushi Kusakabe, my father, the head of the Kusakabe household.
Even though it was an official match, the other disciples will probably never forgive me.
Senpai...
I was on bad terms with my father.
My father didn't like the fact that I looked up to a certain person.
A certain person?
Misao Kusakabe...
The woman known as the greatest female Onmyouji.
However, she broke a law and was banished.
What did she do?
She became a Gehou user.
Gehou?
It's a method that strays from the Kusakabe ways, which has cult spells and even western magic blended in.
The real-life definition of Gehou (外法, げほう) is any religion that strays from Buddhism, as opposed to Naihou (内法, ないほう).
By the way,
This is also a form of Gehou.
Misao-san right now is...?
She was banished seventy years ago.
That means she's already...
No...
Eh?
Maybe...
I might be able to meet her.
Over there.
Eh? By over there, do you mean the Crimson Night?
Kakeru-kun!
Did you do it?
You're going to keep trying until you can do it.
Go back inside.
There's no point in doing this!
Please teach me how to do it with real combat!
No!
It's still too early.
Teach me even if it's too early!
Kakeru-kun...
I don't have time.
While I'm doing this, it's going to happen again...
Go back inside.
Kusakabe-senpai, I...
So they've come.
The one with the eye will probably not awaken.
Put your priority on the disposal of the "fragments".
Understood.
We shall go.
You shall have to go back to your slumber.
Seventy years... no... It may be one hundred years this time.
Entrapped witch.
No... please let me out!
Pitiful...
If only you could experience death.
You-!
I did it!
All right, come!
Don't be so conceited after defeating just a single underling.
Kakeru-kun!
A black knight...
What a nice stance-yono.
This one will definitely not awaken.
If you protect that guy, he'll only drag you down.
Do you want to die early?
I have no intentions of dying!
Even more pitiful than us, who have thrown away our human forms... oh, how entertaining!
Human forms?
Are you implying that you were once human?
And if we are?
Why do you look like that?
You "fragments" have no right to know that!
Run away!
Senpai, but...
Don't fight them blindly.
If you want to protect Yuka Minase, then you must run!
Go!
What are you doing?! Hurry!
You won't escape!
Run and live on.
Kakeru...
Yuka...
Kakeru-kun!
Don't look back!
Run!
They've hidden themselves, huh...
Kakeru-kun...
Shh!
All right, he's gone.
Kakeru-kun!
Dammit!
You can't!
I'll distract him. While I do that, run away!
You'll get killed! It's impossible for you, Kakeru-kun! You'll die!
I'll crush you as you are!
No matter how many times you try, it'll be the same result!
You "fragments" can just disappear!
You've saved me, thank you.
Gula... he underestimated them.
I believe it was that Onmyouji woman who killed him.
Damn them...
Kukuri...nee...san...
Yuka...
Kakeru-kun!
I see... We've returned...
Thank goodness...
Sorry...
It looks like you've regained consciousness.
Kusakabe-senpai...
I'm sorry to have made you worry.
The most important thing is that you're fine.
Satsuki-kun, Yuka-kun, let me introduce you.
She's our new ally.
Next time:
The Mask of a Smile
Could there be an end to this nightmare?
Next Time
The Mask of a Smile