The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
Kakeru-kun....
Kakeru-kun!
Get down!
Are you hurt?
Looks like you're fine, thank goodness.
Who are you?
Let's run!
Yes!
What... is that?
Save me...
The Crystal Maiden
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Rainbow High...
TL Note: Nijikou (虹校) is an abbreviation for 虹陵館学園, the school the main characters attend.
Yeah.
Looks like you two are, too.
There's no secret tricks behind this.
Who in the world are you?
I am Misuzu Kusakabe.
A senior at Rainbow High.
I'm Kakeru Satsuki.
This girl is...
I'm Yuka Minase.
We're both sophomores.
I see.
Nice to meet you.
Thank you for before.
I don't need any thanks.
I only did what was right.
Kusakabe-senpai, what exactly is this world?
Even I don't know.
The only thing for certain is...
This world was created by someone's will,
so the scenery is the same, but...
It exists in a different space-time than the real world.
A different space-time...
Why have we come to this... this Crimson Night?
Crimson Night?
That's not a bad name.
I don't know the true intention, but...
There's no doubt that there's a meaning to this,
and also a reason for being chosen.
Chosen?
Do you two also have some kind of power?
Power?
Something like what you have, Kusakabe-senpai?
We don't have anything like that.
It's them.
Them?
I want to go back, Kakeru-kun.
Rin. Pyou. Tou. Sha. Kai. Jin. Retsu. Zai. Zen.
TL Note: She is chanting the Kuji-in (Nine Hand Seals), a specialized form of Buddhist meditation.
Yuka...
Over there? As I thought.
Huh?
That crystal tower is full of powerful energy.
Perhaps... that place could be the center of this world.
I'm going to the tower.
You two should hide.
I'll go as well!
Kakeru-kun!
You can't, it's dangerous!
Kusakabe-senpai,
I'll go with you!
You'll just be a burden.
What can you do?
You, without any powers.
Damn!
TL Note: Tachibana Dousetsu is the name of a samurai that wielded Raikiri, with which he used to slay a lightning god.
Tachibana Dousetsu,
Lightning Blade!
Run away!
Let's go to that tower.
Kakeru-kun?
Do you want to die?
You two must flee until this Crimson Night is over.
When will it end?
Where's the proof that it will ever end?
It may not end this time.
We might be in here forever!
If there's a chance of escape at that tower, then I want to go!
Do you want to help this girl?
Yes.
Kakeru-kun...
Even if you run and hide, the result is the same, huh?
All right, I understand.
However, I don't know what could be in that tower.
You may not be able to completely protect her.
Even then, are you sure?
Yes!
Yuka, go somewhere and-
I'm going too, don't leave me here!
No matter what happens, I will definitely protect you.
Come!
We're almost there!
Kakeru-kun!
What's wrong?
My eye...!
Can you go on?
Yes.
I cannot let you proceed any further.
So there's also ones that can talk?
If you say that you cannot let us pass...
then that means you have something important to protect there.
I thank you for telling me that.
Strong...
She doesn't have any wasted movements.
As I thought, that girl is...
A girl?
Save me...
Please...
What's your name?
I'm Lisette.
Why do you call out for help?
I'm trapped in here.
Save me... get me out of here!
Don't go.
Lisette is the origin of the energy.
Most likely, she's the person that made this Crimson Night.
Is that true, Lisette?
Did you bring us here?
No.
It wasn't me.
That's a lie.
Send us back!
To the world where we came from!
Please!
I can't.
It's unconscious.
Perhaps it's something inside of Lisette...
It unconsciously activated, created this world, and brought us into it.
Let's save her.
Yuka... but...
She's suffering. Please, Kakeru-kun.
If you say so...
What a weak boy.
You're so similar to Verard Staich, yet so different.
Kakeru-kun...
It's useless.
Within this palace, your skills are unusable.
Now then, shall we have you disappear?
Are all of you those who protect?
Or those who rule?
I have no need to answer "fragments" that will disappear.
"Fragments"?
All of you must not exist.
Especially you!
Invidia!
Run away!
Yuka!
Kakeru-kun!
It's empty...
Here.
What is it? Didn't you go home?
What did you do?
Nothing much.
Do you want me to comfort you?
It's not like that.
You're so insincere.
Have you calmed down a bit?
Yes.
What about Minase-kun?
Somehow...
Geez, I feel like I'm being toyed around with as they please.
Every single time.
Even though I didn't want to be chosen...
"Them."
You said it before, right? "Them."
Could it be that there are others,
people that were also brought into the Crimson Night?
Yeah... there are.
At the very least, there are three others.
But I've only seen the face of one of them.
The other two I caught a glimpse of as they were leaving, out of the corner of my eye.
What kind of people are they?
All three of them are students at Rainbow High.
Two girls and one guy.
Were they running away...
from them?
No, they were fighting with the demons.
Demons?
Yeah.
In Onmyoudou, all wicked beings are called demons.
TL NOTE: Onmyoudou is a practice of spiritual balance based on Wu Xing and Yin and Yang. An Onmyouji is a practitioner of this.
So you're an Onmyouji, right?
It's hereditary.
Those people were not shiki.
TL NOTE: Shiki are a type of spirit summoned by an onmyouji, often invisible to normal people.
Which means... rather than demons, they are spirits of darkness?
An "Ahriman" might be more appropriate.
Ahriman...
Um... so where are the other students?
Yeah, I'll let you meet them.
The one that I saw is a senior.
I also know her name.
If they were fighting...
do they have some kind of power?
So, are they also Onmyouji?
No, that's not it.
About their powers, it'd be better to ask them yourself.
Do I have some kind of power too?
Kakeru-kun...
At that time, that black knight said that I was...
Satsuki-kun, can you try taking that off?
My right eye?
I'm not really certain, but you remember the pain back then, right?
Ahh, right. Now that you mention it, whenever we enter the Crimson Night, my right eye always...
Let me see.
Yes.
Senpai?
Is something wrong?
Minase-kun, don't you feel anything?
Huh?
I see... that's enough, thank you.
You probably haven't awakened yet.
I don't know what kind of power it has...
but I will find out as much as I can about that eye.
I also have some kind of power...
So that means that I also have something.
That's why you were chosen, right? Same for me.
Is it all right if we stay like this?
Yeah.
Are we going to be killed?
When I die, stay by my side.
Stupid!
Don't say stuff like that!
But...!
I'll protect you, Yuka.
I will, for sure.
I found Kakeru!
What're you doing, crossing arms like that?
All lovey dovey?!
T-Tadashi-kun...
Sorry, I couldn't stop him in time!
Kaori-chan!
Aw geez, what the heck are you doing?
Don't fall over all of a sudden! I hit my head, you know!
Ow, I hit my nose.
How exactly could you have hit it?
I don't know, I just did!
Kakeru-kun.
Ah, that's nice!
Kaori, pick me up!
I'll give you a cookie!
Am I some kind of domestic animal?!
What's wrong, Kakeru-kun?
Shiori-san?
Ah, you're here!
I brought her because she asked me to guide her through Shin-Ayame, but she disappeared...
Shiori-chan!
Pick me up!
Or you can ignore me...
Where did you go? We were looking for you!
I was following a cat, then I got lost.
A cat?
Kaori, lift me up! For two cookies!
You're really annoying.
If you want to be picked up, then give me a Yuki-ccho!
TL Note: She's making a reference to the man on the 10,000 yen bill (Yukichi Fukuzawa).
You're a demon bride!
Who are you calling a bride?!
Why do I have to be your bride?!
Stop it!
I'll have them give me a break from work today.
After I greet the master, I'll walk you back home.
Thanks.
Sorry.
Don't worry about it.
Welcome!
I see... so you're a new part-timer here.
Yes. I believe that the master will be back from shopping soon.
Okay.
Excuse me, but have we met you before?
Ah, we might have, because we go to the same school.
So that's how it is.
Ah, I had an accident earlier. I'm quite the klutz.
But I'm all right, so no need to worry.
I'm a Kouryoukan Academy freshman in class C. My name is Yukiko Hirohara.
TL Note: Nijikouryoukan-Gakuen (虹陵館学園) is the full name of the school.
Please call me Yuki-pon!
Yuki-pon?
Yes.
So, what should I call Satsuki-senpai and Minase-senpai by?
Well, isn't "Satsuki-senpai" all right, as usual?
I can't do that!
If I do that, it'd be like we're strangers!
We are strangers...
Huh? Did you just say something?
Ah, nothing, not really.
You can call me Yuka.
Yup! Affirmative.
All right then. I'll call Minase-senpai "Yuka-san."
And Satsuki-senpai is...
Ka-cchan!
Can you at least call me Kakeru-senpai?
Yup, affirmative!
All right then, that's what it'll be.
Ah, I'll pour you some coffee.
Yukiko special! I just perfected it a while ago, it's really tasty!
Just wait a little bit.
After talking with Yukiko-chan, it's already this late.
It's all right, I already called Mom.
Wanna come over?
No, I'll go home for today. I'm tired, after all.
I see.
It's a good thing that we're the only ones having hard times.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
That was just an illusion...
Kukuri-san.
That's why it's better not to worry about it.
I guess so, thanks.
If the Crimson Night comes again...
don't move until I come, okay?
Yeah, got it.
Kakeru-kun...
Yuka...
Can I... really protect Yuka?
I want to protect her... but...
With the way I am right now...
Again...
Kouryoukan-Gakuen
Library Room
The Girl of the Crystalline Palace
Save me...
Hey!
Yuka.
Geez... you disappeared without a word, so I panicked.
Ah... sorry.
Were you looking it up?
I doubt that there's an answer, but...
I couldn't just stand there not doing anything.
I see. I'll help search too, then.
Okay.
Strange Tales From the North (Vol. 1)
Strange Tales From the North (Vol. 2)
The Dragon King and Me
Diverged
World
Forgotten -
The Door to Another World
Past Space and Time
Crimson
Darkness
Kakeru-kun!
What happened?
It's not an illusion.
She was there.
Right now, here.
Nee-san was here!
You are the one who awakened
the devil.
Could this be?
My eye!
Kakeru-kun!
You are the one who awakened
the devil.
Kakeru-kun!
A black... moon...
Next time:
Lonely Pride.
Is there an answer at the end of the nightmare?
Next Time
Lonely Pride