I'm sorry... I'm sorry...
T-Takahisa-senpai...
Takahisa-senpai...!
The Awakening of a Witch
The black knights are just.
That's right.
Then you're saying that we're the evil ones!?
That's messed up!
"Fragment"...
Yes. You are "fragments."
Fragments of the Voidstone that holds enormous magical power.
Voidstone...
I am also one of those "fragments."
To be exact, one who holds a "fragment."
There are seven fragments.
You... Me...
Yuka-san... Yukiko-san...
Kukuri-san... Takahisa-san...
And finally, the prisoned Witch.
Is the fragment a demonic essence?
The fragments themselves aren't necessarily demonic.
However, if the seven are to be gathered once again...
their power will be overwhelming.
In other words, it all depends on who uses them.
Is that Lisette's objective?
In order to collect all seven fragments,
she called us into her world, the Crimson Night?
That is correct.
So then everything lies with Lisette?
Help me...
That is not her real form.
When she was sealed, her powers and memory were taken and she took that form.
Her real name is Liselotte.
Liselotte...
When all seven fragments are gathered, she will be able to grant a wish.
A wish?
The Descent to Hell.
What you call the black moon is the Gate of Oblivion.
It is the entrance to Hell.
Liselotte is trying to open the Gate of Oblivion using the powers of the Voidstone.
If the entrance were to open, what'll happen?
The world will descend into Hell.
In other words, fall to ruins. Right?
Yes.
The world will... fall to ruins...
And in order to hinder that, the Black Knights are targeting us?
In order to save the world...
I see that. They're just, aren't they.
However, they already don't have enough fragments left.
Takahisa...
But the "fragment" is still there.
As long as Aeon's Eye exists, the Descent to Hell is still possible.
The tea is ready.
We also have cookies, Kakeru-kun.
Here, have some.
Yuka...
Do you believe we can win?
Misuzu-senpai...
That's not it, Kakeru-kun.
You should call her Kusakabe-senpai.
Note: Yuka wants Kakeru to call Misuzu in a more formal way: with her last name.
What's wrong?
Oh, no, nothing.
Sorry. I'm a bit tired so I'll just rest a bit.
Yuka, I'll take my tea.
Yes.
Shiori-kun, let's continue our conversation later.
Senpai...
Are you fine without resting either, Kakeru-kun?
You're tired, right?
Well, yeah.
Maybe we can sleep together, like we did in the past.
Idiot. What are you saying?
What's wrong? Your face is going red.
You're strange, Kakeru-kun.
The world will fall to ruin...
That's just way too much for me to absorb right now.
Kakeru-kun.
Y-Yuka?
Let's sleep together.
H-Hey!
Let her sleep.
If you do so, then I can continue my story.
A hundred years in the past, a single magician obtained an immortal body.
People called her the Witch of Babylon.
They feared and hated her.
So that's Liselotte.
Eventually, the Witch met with a young king and fell in love.
The name of that king was Verard.
At that time, the storm of civil war was sweeping through the county of Dravenia.
This world should just fall to ruin.
That's right. We don't need this kind of world.
I don't need anything as long as I have you.
Kakeru-kun...
Afterwards, Verard was felled by one of his trusted friend's retainers.
He lost his life.
Lisellote wept when she learned of his death.
And so she swore:
"I will fulfill my loved one's wish with my hands."
Descent to Hell.
And so we, the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum,
have traversed time and fought with those allied with the Witch that brings misfortune to the world.
Now, 64 years before the present,
we succeeded at last in sealing her into an alternate world...
...in this very land.
So that's why the Crimson Night is in this city.
However, the people who risked their lives to fight for the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Probitorum Holy Ministry have,
as a price for sealing her, been transformed into grotesque forms.
The black knights.
They are protecting the Witch's seal in the alternate world holding Liselotte in which you call the Crimson Night.
So that's what this was all about?
Kakeru-kun...
The blacks knights believe that Verard will eventually awaken within you, take over your body, and help the Witch using the Aeon's Eye.
That's why they want to kill you before that happens.
Verard will take over my body...
That is what our Holy Ministry believes.
With the Aeon's Eye, it is possible to not only seal,
but get rid of the immortal Witch in time altogether.
The reason why I had observed without revealing myself was to determine whether you're a human to be doubted, or...
...you're a human that can be trusted with the world's future.
And the answer is?
I had thought, "What a naive and weak human this is."
"Such a human would surely have their soul and body stolen by Verard, as we thought."
But I have come to believe.
Actually, I too have been pessimistic of this world.
"What a pointless world," I thought.
Thus, after getting assigned this task, I had thought that had worse come to worst, then it would be my fate.
However...
I had come to know that this world and its people still had plenty of life within.
Sensei, there's an idiot sleeping during class!
Therefore I will believe in you.
You who lives in this world, creates bonds
between people, and embraces tomorrow...
For friends and for tomorrow.
Can you do this?
I want to. If it is possible, I want to protect this world.
But Shiori-san, had it been yesterday, I believe that I could have answered that.
That it was all right because I had friends.
But... now it's...
Now we're... all in pieces.
Tachibana-senpai...
Are you all right?
Yes. Oh, that's right. I have to apologize.
I had misunderstood... about the message.
I'm sorry.
It's
fine
Thank you.
Is that you, Kakeru?
Yes.
How's Yuka?
She fell asleep while we were out there in the sun.
I carried her into the living room.
Sit down.
Yes.
I had lived up until now by thinking only about how to fight.
"I want to become strong."
"I want to become better at being an Onmyouji than anyone else."
That's why I studied alone, ignoring everything else.
I lived while chasing after the legendary Onmyouji,
Kusakabe Misao, that I had known about since childhood.
I must've been so naive to think that I could have won...
That maybe I could have passed Misao the way I am now.
I was so childish that it's pathetic.
She showed me that...
I can't win against Misao.
Senpai...
We're in different leagues, Kakeru.
Misao and I...
Misao had learned from experience with other people.
Compared to that, I have always secluded and taught myself alone.
I had only yearned for knowledge.
What's so wrong with that?
I'm just a speculator.
Since I don't have any experience, I imagine it in my head.
The knowledge learned from paper and the sensation of learning through the body...
Which do you think is better?
Misao had read all of my actions.
All I could do was move in a way that gets easily read like the texts I've studied.
No way. I believe that you're thinking too much into this.
Is that right?
Maybe that's right.
It's just as you see.
I'm a pitiful speculator.
The reason why I was able to use the Aeon's Eye is thanks to you.
You taught me not through papers but through the sword...
...with your body.
Wouldn't the first feeling you perceive when you meet the person you so admire be nervousness?
And so you end up not feeling like yourself.
Or rather, you can't stay calm about it.
That's why...
I'm sorry. I can't express it well.
But...
Thank you.
That's right. Thank you, Kakeru.
Senpai...
Come over here.
Kakeru-kun...
Where's Kakeru-kun?
Probably in the toilet.
I believe he'll come back soon enough.
Just a bit. Just a little bit...
Misuzu-senpai...
Please...
Yes.
He's pretty late. I'm gonna go look for him.
Kakeru-kun!
So you were awake?
Where did you go?
I took a walk around the garden. Why?
It's all right then.
Kakeru-kun, come here for a bit.
What's wrong?
Just come!
I knew it. I liked Takahisa-senpai.
I loved him.
Hey, Yuka. You shouldn't just enter here without permission!
It's all right.
Hug me.
Yuka...
Please.
A parallel world?
To seal the Witch away, the disciples used a forbidden magic:
The Rainbow of the Covenant.
It splits and diverts the enemy's magic into seven worlds, thus weakening them.
That skill was used 64 years ago to obstruct the Descent to Hell?
And in return, seven fragments were born and scattered to their respective parallel worlds.
The fragments were originally split into seven different worlds?
But right now...
When a scattered fragment was first thrown into the Crimson Night, the rest were all gathered together.
And so for some reason, when the Crimson Night ended, all the fragments had again gathered into one world.
So this is that world...
You smell of that person.
That smell... I'll erase that smell.
Yuka...
If you say that there were fragments each in their own
respective worlds, then to whom does this world belong?
As long as you're here, that's fine.
As long as you're here, everything is fine with me.
Yuka....
Don't you think so too, Kakeru-kun?
As long as I'm around, everything is fine, right?
You'll be fine without your big sister anymore, right?
Sister?
There is nothing to be surprised about. This Kukuri-san is an illusion.
An illusion?
If it were someone that had originally held a fragment in this world...
they can influence the world's structure with the power of the fragment.
So that means...
The illusion that Yuka-san created for Kakeru...
The real Kukuri-san that had held a fragment has already died in her own world.
So this actually Yuka's world?
You doesn't have to fight anymore.
I'll protect you.
Yuka...
Yukiko!
For you to have appeared by yourself...
I can't forgive you.
I can't ever forgive you.
And what are you going to do about it?
I'll kill you!
Senpai!
Yukiko went alone into the crystal tower!
What did you say?
Let's go!
I won't let you go.
Yuka?
You'll be fine as long as you're with me.
I'll protect you!
Yuka...
I'll go on ahead.
I'll be waiting for you!
Yuka, did I do something wrong?
Is it because of me that you...
My weapon is...
Don't hurt my Kakeru-kun!
Kakeru-kun...
Yuka...
I continued to fight because I wanted to protect you.
You are precious to me.
That feeling won't change.
But there's something else important to me right now.
Everyone, I'm coming now.
Senpai...
Takahisa-senpai...
Takahisa...
You are no match for me.
Yukiko... Why did you have to go ahead...
Misuzu-senpai!
Shiori-san!
Kakeru!
Superbia, other fragments are coming.
Settle this.
You were able to heal your wounds, right?
But that was just the power of the fragment of Void that you hold.
Let's have you turn back into a human.
Let's grant your wish.
Die!
Yukiko!
A fragment of Void...
She pulled it out?
Damn you!
Stop it!
I'll pull out your right eye, too.
Avaritia-sama!
The fragment...
Yuka...
Don't tell me...
I'll save you.
Liselotte...
Next time: The Choice Called Ruin
There was no answer at the end of the nightmare!
Next Time
The Choice Called Ruin