The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
You're annoying!
Oh man, he's from our school.
Was it a fight?
Unbelievable.
As I thought, time hasn't passed in this world, huh?
Isn't that nice? You lot can take it easy.
The Mask of a Smile
Welcome, everyone!
To all who want to join,
throw away all your desires!
I am Yukiko Hirohara, the Study of Modern Societies Club president!
By "study of modern societies," I mean more or less the specific investigative research on all things of modern society!
In other words, the modern version of classic literature!
I've already heard that many times.
All right! Our "study of modern societies" members are...
Not only that, but two girls and one guy!
It's impossible.
My sister died seven years ago.
What I saw in the Crimson Night had to be an illusion.
Still, at that time...
Kakeru-kun, something wrong?
It's not good to be brooding over it.
After all, everyone's gathered here.
That's right.
I'm so happy! I've made a lot of friends!
Yukiko-chan, you're incredible.
You've managed to survive all alone in the Crimson Night, right?
Yes.
Does that mean that you have some kind of special power?
I'm just a normal girl.
When I snap, though, I'm scary!
You're always so cheerful, Yukiko-chan.
Since that's my only good quality!
Jeez...
Where and with whom do you fight to get injuries like these?
You barely have enough attendance.
You're frequently late to school, too...
Do you have any intention of graduating?
You're so noisy, you unmarried, no-guy woman!
Takahisa...
I'm very happy that you don't hit women.
Hold it! Hold it right there, Takahisa!
"Fragments".
The black knights called us "fragments".
I have no need to answer a fragment that will soon disappear.
What do they mean by "fragments"?
Also, how many "fragments" are there?
Yes!
I know one of them.
When I first came to the Crimson Night,
I was saved by someone who looked like a hero of justice.
Did you meet her too, Yukiko-kun?
That person is not a "her".
That person is a guy!
Like I could say anything to her. About that world...
...or about this power, too...
Takahisa!
You're not getting away!!
You're annoying!
All right! It's decided!
For today's agenda, let's go and look for that person!
If we decide fast, everything can be done quickly.
Let's go!
Sorry, I'll just be in here for a sec...
Where did you go, Takahisa!? Where are you!?
That was a close call.
Ouch... What now, all of a sudden?
That was mean!
You're Mr. Hero of Justice!
Glasses girl? You again?
Y-Yeah.
Everyone, the search is over.
Huh?
It's this person!
What a surprise.
For there to be this many people that can see the black moon...
You're Satsuki, right?
What is it?
Do you really have no powers?
You've done pretty well surviving up to now.
That's quite something.
What!?
Don't get mad!
I'm complimenting you.
You want some sweet potato chips?
No.
I don't want any.
I'm fine.
All right then! I'll take you up on that.
So anyways...
There hasn't been anyone sucked into the Crimson Night that knows any details, huh...
All right, I'm off.
Just a minute, Takahisa Tajima!
Aren't you going to join our study of modern societies club?
The weak dogs band together.
It's not my hobby to gather with the weak.
Did he say dog?!
What if the Crimson Night comes again?
I will manage... all by myself.
Kakeru-kun...
What a rude guy.
Nope.
Even though he looks like that, he's actually quite kind.
That's right.
He's really nice.
It's not disgusting. In fact, everyone would be jealous.
Kakeru-senpai!
If you just flail around aimlessly, you won't hit her!
The more you hurry, the worse your swordsmanship gets!
For what reason do you fight?
That is...
...to protect Yuka.
What a futile ring it has.
They just slip through your mouth and aren't becoming flesh and blood.
Your feelings aren't turning into power.
Did you have the resolution in your sword?
Resolution?
Resolution is the acquisition of comprehension.
Right now, you don't fully comprehend the circumstances.
First to train is not your body but your heart.
Change feelings into strength.
Think only about that!
Yes!
Change my feelings into strength...
I want strength.
Strength to protect Yuka.
Yuka!
Kakeru-senpai?
What's wrong, Kakeru-kun?
Uh... nothing...
What was I doing?
Let me just say that...
If we were to get into a battle right now, while trying to protect Yuka, you would die immediately!
Is that so... figures.
Ah, sorry, it just slipped out!
No.
It's the truth.
Kakeru-kun...
To test Kakeru-kun's resolution...
I was thinking of pointing my sword at her.
Those movements right now were...
The one who woke up the demon is you.
Hey, Yuka...
Eh?
Right now, I'm pitifully powerless,
but I will protect you no matter what.
Don't overdo it, okay?
I don't have any kind of powers either.
It's all right... as long you stay by my side...
I also think that this is for myself.
I want to protect you.
I want to turn that desire into strength.
Kakeru-kun...
Oh! Hello!
Good morning, Shiori!
Nice to meet you. How are you doing, Shiori?
How much does it cost?
Please don't desecrate Italian.
But I want to be able to be in love with a demon.
Please burn. Burn until you turn to ashes.
Understood!
Hey, Shiori-chan, you're into the whole "ladies-first" thing, right?
I'll listen to anything you say!
Please continue on this road and...
...go turn right and die.
My pleasure!
Continue on this road and...
...turn righ-
Carbonara!
TL NOTE: Carbonara is an Italian sauce, usually with spaghetti or pasta, that has black pepper.
Arrivederci.
Good bye.
What a completely and utterly dramatic moron.
Right?
If he gets any dumber than this, who knows what he'll say next.
Kusakabe-senpai!
Hey.
Yuka went ahead already.
Kakeru-kun,
about yesterday's practice...
Yes?
No, never mind.
Y-Yuka...
Good work today!
The study of modern societies club is having a study session right now.
The... modern... societies... club... study... session?
Yes. Why does Yuka-san have such large breasts...
...even though she has such a childish figure?
Stop it, Yukiko-chan!
She isn't pushing them together or raising them up!
Without a push-up bra, this is a modern miracle!
In such a pure school... what shameless actions!
Hey, Yukiko-chan, stop! ... I said stop...
It's coming!
The Crimson Night...
That's...
He's fighting... Takahisa-senpai.
What?
Burn in hell!
Takahisa-senpai is a psychic fire energy user, a pyrokinesist.
A black knight!
You won't get away this time, "fragments"!
What the hell are you all?!
I have nothing to say to the walking dead.
Questions are useless, huh?
Yukiko-kun, I'll leave these two in your care.
Yes!
Kannagiri Nagamitsu.
Prepare yourself!
This guy... he uses martial arts?
He's fast!
Kusakabe-senpai is being pushed back!
So it's begun, huh.
Yes, Avaritia-sama.
To have defeated Gula...
Those damned "fragments".
Please do not worry.
This time, it's Ira and Invidia.
Also, I, Superbia, will go as well.
Kakeru-kun!
I'm fine.
Forget that, senpai is...
Misuzu-senpai is in a pinch, right?
If only I had some power...
I don't believe that they wished to have those powers.
They had no choice but to accept their powers.
It's that kind of horror.
I'll be going!
Y-Yukiko-chan...
This speed is...!
What an unbelievable fighting ability.
Damn you!
Yukiko-kun!
Little girl, don't mess with me!
What?
Yukiko-chan?!
It's like she's a different person...
No!!!
Yukiko!!
Ira.
So it's you, Invidia?
I though that you'd be enough to slay the "fragments", but...
You can all just die together!
Hold it right there!
The ally of justice has arrived.
My face is...!
How dare you!
I'll kill you!
The Crimson Night is ending...!
I'll remember this.
Next time we meet, I'll definitely...
We made it...
What's wrong, Yuka?
Kakeru-kun...!
Ridiculous... with that severe wound...?!
I've really done it, huh?
Yukiko?
Yukiko-chan!
I become like that when I take off my glasses.
A double personality?
Yeah.
Superhuman fighting abilities and a terrifying blood thirst...
Where did you obtain those abilities?
Those, huh? I don't really want to talk about that, though...
More importantly, Yukiko-chan, are you okay?
She's healed!
The truth is, I am able to regenerate!
I have been unable to die since birth.
You can't die?
Yes. Disgusting, aren't I?
It's all right. I'm used to it. Since a long time ago, everyone has...
I was born in the country of Dransvania.
There, in a millenium of blood of massacre...
That's enough.
It's all right, Yukiko.
Now there's four people who have accepted me. Everyone here, and...
It's not disgusting. In fact, everyone would be jealous.
Even if you get hurt, you can return back to normal afterwards.
Back to the pretty girl you were before!
Yukiko-chan.
Thank you very much, Yuka-san, Kakeru-senpai, Misuzu-senpai.
And also...
Takahisa-senpai!
I'll be awaiting your bravery!
Next time:
For Friends and Tomorrow.
Could there be an end to this nightmare?
Next Time
For Friends and Tomorrow