Ahh, the powers of darkness are embracing me...
It feels very nostalgic.
Liselotte Wreckmeister...
Good for you!
Very well.
I shall grant...
...your wish!
Yuka!
Kakeru!
Hell no!
You saw the future?
Such insolence!
You can wander about in limbo with your loved one for eternity.
I will not hand over any more fragments to you!
Superbia!
Kill the owner of the Aeon's Eye!
You mustn't kill him!
Fools.
Do you really think you can defeat me now?
Liselotte...
Will you kill me?
Have you forgotten about my immortality?
I understand now.
Without enough fragments, the only thing that can grant your desires...
...is this right eye of mine.
That's right.
Therefore, there's only one way to save Yuka... everyone... the world!
No!
I have to die!!
Kakeru-kun!
Dawn of the Dark Night
Kukuri-neesan...
Yuka...
What're you reading?
Is it funny?
The end...
I like the ending.
"And so, they both lived happily ever after."
Me too!
Kakeru-kun...
You're dull!
You're creepy!
Wait, Yuka!
Don't!
Who's she?!
Grr!
Let's go home!
Oh?
Yuka-chan?
What's with your clothes?!
It's nothing.
No, something did happen! What? What happened?
Kakeru-kun! Let's go to the park!
Don't wanna.
Let's read a book in your room then!
Yuka-chan...
You should eat something.
Here, have some.
Shut up!
Oh no, they're ruined. I'll go get some more, okay?
Kakeru-kun...
I'm here...
I'm here for you... I always will be.
It's all right.
Yuka...
Are you awake?
Misuzu-senpai... What happened?
You should thank Yuka.
When you stabbed yourself in the throat with Raikiri, Yuka used her powers to make Raikiri disappear.
She saved you.
She did?
Liselotte temporarily lost her powers.
That gave Shiori and I a small opening in order to carry you and Yuka here.
Is she okay?
She's fatigued from using her powers.
It's also probably from the shock as well.
Kakeru, you are an utter fool for trying to take your own life.
"And so, they both lived happily ever after."
I thought I understood, but apparently not.
I'm so stupid.
Kakeru...
I have to live. No matter the cost, I have to stay by Yuka's side.
While I'm still alive, I need to repay her for everything she's ever done for me...
...plus interest.
In order to do that, I have to defeat Liselotte!
For friends and for tomorrow.
"While I'm still alive", huh...
Shiori-san...
Kukuri! Why are you here?
Weren't you just an illusion that Yuka made?
This Kukuri-san is different to the one in Yuka-san's world.
I am Abraxus.
A spirit that resided in your sister's body.
A spirit in her body?
Why?
In order to seek vengeance.
My master, Satsuki Kukuri, took her own life.
She thought that without the necessary number of fragments, Liselotte would be unable to perform the Descent to Hell.
She knew about the Descent to Hell?!
She did.
That's why she killed her little brother, the holder of the Aeon's Eye,
and then herself.
She killed me?
Yes.
But then... Why is Kakeru alive?
I was the one who killed you.
I'm sorry, Kakeru.
Abraxus killed Kakeru-san.
But that Kakeru-san did not possess the Aeon's Eye.
The Kakeru-san who did possess it was in a world different from Kukuri's.
Yuka's world?
That's right. This is why you are still alive.
Neither a fragment nor Abraxus resided in the body of the Kukuri-san that was in Yuka-san's world.
That's why she simply just took her own life.
Wait, I lost you...
Put simply...
Two different Kukuri-sans in two different worlds both knew about the Decent to Hell, and both took the same course of action.
The Kukuri-san who possessed a fragment used Abraxus to kill Kakeru.
But Yuka's world's Kukuri-san didn't have Abraxus, so she couldn't kill Kakeru with her own hands.
This living Kakeru is you, and you were the sole owner of the Aeon's Eye all along.
I believe that you were originally with the Kukuri-san that did possess a fragment.
However, due to some development, Yuka-san used her fragment's power to call you over to her world.
Subconsciously, anyways.
So the one Kukuri-san talked to was...
Me.
I talked about the truth with Kukuri-san in not just two worlds, but six.
I could not figure out just which world's Kukuri-san possessed the fragment, after all.
You can traverse space-time?
Yes.
Why did you only tell her?
At the time that I received my orders, only Kukuri-san was old enough to understand me.
So you told my sister to die in order to protect the world?!
No, I did not. All I did was warn her.
I did not think she would actually do that.
Don't, Kakeru.
I gravely apologize.
Even now I believe that intervention was the worst action I could have taken.
The clock!
Yuka!
The roof!
We're not in the Crimson Night...
The master of this world is here.
Yuka!
So she's sealed Yuka-san's power.
So you've no more intention of taking your own life, Satsuki Kakeru?
Good.
Give Yuka back!
If you come here, sure.
Come.
Kakeru!
How obedient.
Give her back.
Kakeru-kun...
The black moon is...!
Now, let us all succumb to the Descent to Hell.
Kakeru!
Let's believe that the black knights will have a change of heart.
Right!
Don't interfere!
Damn you!
Bastard!
Kakeru-kun!
Kakeru!
Are you all right?
Y-Yeah...
Take my fragment...
A doll?!
She wasn't a human?
No, she is. Only her heart was not artificial.
Her fragment.
Shiori-san's fragment...
She is betting everything on you by giving that to you.
If you have that, you may be able to seal off Liselotte.
Shiori possessed the power to traverse space-time.
If you combine her powers with the Aeon's Eye, you may be able to seal Liselotte away in a dimensional rift.
It is certainly worth trying.
Why did you save Kakeru? Weren't you trying to kill him?
The chances of saving this world are now close to zero.
In that case, there is nothing left to be done but believe.
We cannot afford to be arguing. Avaritia-sama's seal on her is growing weaker by the second.
Resistance is futile.
Kakeru-kun!
I'm sorry I couldn't protect you.
You're wrong, Yuka.
Protecting is my job. I will protect you, Yuka.
Forever and ever!
Kakeru-kun!
The sealed gate of enlightenment...
The heavenly bodies seven, instilling power upon Gaea...
Ye shalt chant naught the hymn of war, but swiftly mine will consummate.
Wielding the power of one thousand generations...
Shinuchi Doujigiri Yasutsuna!
真打 童子切　安綱: "True Blade"
Child Killer, forged by blacksmith Yasutsuna.
The life-devouring sword, Doujigiri...
I'll become your shield, Kakeru!
I see. You love him as well...
In the end, a human's heart is what determines whether to destroy or protect.
She's here!
Avaritia-sama!
Now, let's end this.
I won't let you.
What?
I won't let you end it.
This is just the beginning!
Hope is nothing more than a fleeting dream that you will wake to despair from.
Bullshit!
Just when I'd figured out my mistake...
Just when I'd decided on changing myself...
Why are you trying to take away our tomorrow?!
Kakeru-kun...
I will not give up, no matter who says otherwise!
I will not believe that there's only despair waiting for us after that "fleeting dream"!
Good things and bad things may be in store for us...
Friends and enemies may be lying in wait for us...
If there's something bad, then just do something about it!
If you give up, then that's just going to be the end of it!
Such childish banter.
That's right! My words might sound like nonsense to you,
but that's what I think! I believe that our tomorrow will come!
I thought I was alone... and I was prepared to live accordingly.
But that's not true. I've been supported by everyone all along.
Yuka was there for me. I was able to remain sane because she was at my side.
It's thanks to her!
Kakeru-kun...
I will protect our world... our tomorrow!
Protect it if you can.
Liselotte.
Verard?
A thought from the Aeon's Eye!
That's enough.
You must not take away these children's future.
Verard... What do you mean?
I was wrong. I was not truly looking at the hearts of men.
This boy showed me the light.
Please understand, Liselotte. You must not destroy this world!
Verard...
I no longer have any doubts.
What my eight hundred years of solitude desires is a piece of the Emerald Tablet, the Aeon's Eye!
Emerald Tablet: An ancient text purporting to reveal the secret of ylem (primordial substance) and its transmutations.
Senpai!
What are you doing?! Focus, Misuzu!
Douji, O Douji!
Devour mine flesh...
Deliver unto the great evil a demon's sacred flame!
Kigazettou!
鬼牙絶刀: Demon Fang Executioner
It's useless!
You little...
I don't think so!
Fall unto eternal slumber, Witch of Babylon!
Let me go! Let me go!!
No!!
Avaritia-sama...
Yuka...
What's happening?
With its master gone, the Crimson Night can no longer remain stable.
It's fine. I will transport you out.
So a future like this actually existed...
Misuzu, I'll entrust the Kusakabe household to you.
Yes.
Thank you...
Yuka!
Damn you, Kakeru! You're trying to keep Yuka-rin all to yourself again!
That's no good! Let me join in on the fun too!
Don't go spouting off nonsense! Idiot.
Not a word about the Crimson Night was spoken between Yuka and I ever since.
And when I opened that tumbling doll,
there was a smaller tumbling doll inside of it!
When I opened that small doll, an even smaller one was in it!
Takahisa!
You grabbed some cash again from my wallet, didn't you?!
Crud!
Ah, Takahisa-senpai! I wasn't done talking...
I'll make you pay with your body, you runt!
It was only 150 yen!
It doesn't matter! Hold it!
Yukiko and Takahisa didn't know either of us.
Kukuri-neesan and Shiori-san are also absent.
Hey.
Misuzu-senpai!
I'm headed to Ayanas. Wanna come?
Sure!
I don't know whose world this is. All I know is that it's peaceful.
It's really nice out, eh?
Hmm? Ah, yeah, it is.
If that isn't the future...
...then this world will have a tomorrow.
Will you come tomorrow?