Good
room as
kids
much
darken
as
the
possible
Good
room as
kids
much
darken
as
the
possible
Good
room as
kids
much
darken
as
the
possible
Good
room as
kids
much
darken
as
the
possible
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
Good
room as
kids
much
darken
as
the
possible
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
and
of
watch
48,000
from a
light
distance
years.
Just kidding.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
Should the setting or
characters be different,
please do not get angry.
We beg of you.
Ew, Kakeru-kun! Don't look!
Did you see?
Ah, no, I didn't.
So you did.
Er...
Sorry.
You looked because you wanted to, right?
Then it's fine.
Yuka...
Kakeru-kun!
Pink Phantasmagoria
This is...
It's not the Crimson Night!
Pink Night?!
Kusakabe-senpai!
Yukiko-chan!
Are you all right?
Thank goodness.
Why is everything pink?!
Senpai, what on earth is this?
I don't know.
All I do know is that we've wandered into some completely different world.
Different world?
Kakeru-kun!
Senpai!
Are you okay?
Y-Yes...
Somehow.
What's wrong?
Kakeru-kun?
Why are you blushing?
Uh, your clothes...
Eh? Clothes?
Uh, nothing...
Tell us, Kakeru-kun.
I-It's nothing...
Can it be that you can...
...see through our clothes?
N-No, that's not it...
Don't lie!
Kakeru-kun!
I'm sorry! I can see!
Underwear, or bare?!
U-Underwear.
Oh, just underwear? Thank god.
This is not all right!
※Please enjoy the view through the Aeon's Eye Camera※
But what's going on, really?
Kakeru's power should be foresight, but...
※Please enjoy the view through the Aeon's Eye Camera※
Is it because of this world?
Um, aren't you going to cover yourself?
My underwear is covering everything, so no problem.
Don't look, Kakeru-kun!
You should just put your eyepatch back on.
Shiori-san!
No, don't look~!
Takahisa!
Kakeru-kun, put this on!
R-Right...
Hurry!
Huh...
Hurry~!
Shut up!
Kakeru-kun!
Ah, sorry.
Wow.
No!
E-Eyepatch...
"Jiggle"?
That's my chest...
Oh, my bad!
Ew, Kakeru-kun~!
Takahisa!!
Ass!
Kakeru-kun!
Sorry.
How long are you going to stand there?!
YES!
Are you okay?
Sheesh.
So it's like this... It seems that everyone's powers have taken on a distorted form in this world.
Our powers have?
Let's see...
Yukiko-chan, you'll go berserk!
Yuka!
Yuka-san, you're so smooth! It feels so nice!
D-Don't, Yukiko-chan!
Your ears are so soft...
Stop it!
Y-Yukiko-chan!
Y-Yukiko-chan...
I see. Distorted powers, all right.
Yes.
You okay?
Y-Yeah...
So that's a French kiss...
Oh, it's nothing.
What, you want me to try?
You don't have to if you don't want.
That just makes me want to even more.
Water?
Aw, that's not sexy at all!
Ooh, I know!
How's that?
I don't give a damn...
So that means Yuka's powers are also...
I'm scared, Kakeru-kun!
That was a nice nap.
Oh? They're here.
Dark Spirits!
W-What?!
They're tiny!
They're kinda cute!
I wanna keep one!
Fools! Dark Spirits are all dangerous!
Here I come!
Ooh, we've got a winner!
N-No it's not...
It's vibrating, eh?
That was unnecessary...
Is that your only katana shaped like that?
Ah, I wanna see your others! Let's see how many different ones there are!
Misuzu-senpai, please bring them all out!
Don't screw around! This isn't the time for that!
Oh, the Dark Spirits all ran away in sight of that thing.
Kakeru-kun, you're rather calm...
Eh? Calm? Why?
Huh? Don't tell me that you don't know what this is?
This is... um...
That, right?
Yup, it's that.
Kakeru-kun!
Um...
You serious?
Oh, come on!
It's fine if you don't know. It's not embarrassing at all.
Minase, explain it to him.
Eh?! T-That's...
It's pretty hard for a girl to explain it orally, eh?
I'll explain it.
Kukuri-san!
Hello.
H-Hello...?
What's with those clothes?!
Oh? Is something wrong?
It's super sexy!
Thanks.
Wait a minute... You can actually talk, Kukuri-san?
It seems so.
Another distorted form...
All's good! I'm lovin' these distortions!
Kukuri, put on some clothes!
These aren't clothes?
No they aren't!
Okay, I'll go change after I explain it to them then.
Save the explanation for later! Hurry!
I won't take long.
This is a v*******. A toy used by females for sexual pleasure.
Kukuri!
Its usage is the same as the real thing:
Getting it e**** and then thrusting in and out your v*****.
Like real s**, it stimulates your c*******, causing an o***** that gives you a great amount of pleasure.
Having it put straight like that gives even me the shudders...
Yeah...
It comes in many shapes, such as m**** w***-shaped, b********-shaped, or for extra playfulness,
there are even r*****-shaped ones as well.
That's enough!
I was just about to get to the good part...
I'm sorry!
I had no idea...
It's fine. It's not knowledge that just anyone could know about.
But...
So don't apologize.
Yuka...
Kakeru-kun...
You two, get a room...
What's that?!
That's...
Black... Knights?
We are the Pink Rangers, Erotica Five!
Erotica Carnation Pink!
Erotica Amaranth Pink!
Erotica Lavender Pink!
Erotica Cherry Pink!
Erotica Rose Pink!
That's confusing...
We shall protect the pink of this world! We are the Erotica Five!
O...kay...
Let's pretend we never saw this...
This world is really screwed up, huh?
Whose world is it anyway?
Let's head to the crystal towers. If we go to this world's center, we might understand something.
She's writing something.
Hearing her talk makes me dizzy, so I told her that if she wants to say something, write it down in that sketchbook.
What's up? Did something happen?
I didn't give it to you to play around with!
What, that's not it?
There's something written here.
There is?
So you did have something to say.
Show us that first!
So what's it say?
"Yoshifumi then took a deep breath and lowered his lips to Tamaki's tender pink flower petal―"
Isn't this an ero novel?!
Hey, Yuka...
What was that drawing?
Who was that?!
Someone's been captured!
Okay, let's go!
Stop right there!
W-Wanna join us, kiddies?
Silence, you dirty suit of armor!
How the hell can you feel this through that?!
Yes! Yes, that's the spot!
Hurry and take that off so I can use you for my experiments!
Oh, Mama Mia!
Yes, do whatever you want to my body!
Retreat!!
What the hell is with this world?!
Kakeru-kun, I wanna go home!
We can, right? We'll be fine, right?
Yeah, it's fine. We'll definitely get out of this, Yuka.
Thank goodness... We can pick up where we left off.
Left off where?
You sure can drink, Takahisa-senpai!
Is that water even potable?
What? Yeah, of course it is!
It's coming outta me, after all!
I see! So it's okay, then!
You're fine with that reason...?
C'mon, have some too!
Eh? Are you sure?
Don't hold back!
Okay, then I humbly accept!
I know what you want to say.
Yes, I know already. You don't have to draw it out for me.
Kusakabe-senpai!
Where are you going?
Well... Anywhere but here.
You seem stressed.
You can use that, then.
Pink Hot Springs
This isn't the time to goof off in a hot spring!
We never know when those Dark Spirits will attack us!
You mean these guys?
So cute!
It seems they have no intention of attacking us.
Senpai!
What're you so angry about?
She's really serious.
She can't fully accept this situation, huh...
I haven't fully accepted it either, but...
I guess she can't help but stress after what's happened so far.
Yeah. We don't know whose world this is, or whether we can ever get out of it.
She's one who wouldn't fare too well in the world out there, huh?
Kusakabe-senpai!
Are you stupid?!
Kukuri-san's trying to cheer her up in her own way, eh?
She's only succeeded in irritating her further, though.
Senpai, there's no enemies here, so let's go for a soak!
NO!!
Anyway, I've gotta calm down and think about our situation again.
Ooh, a hot spring!
Senpai...
I feel sorry for her...
Misuzu-san, it's time to let your hair down.
Okay, let's jump in!
Oh, let's decide by rock-paper-scissors then!
Huh? Why?
To decide whether girls or boys go first, of course...
What're you going on about? Let's go altogether!
Together is kinda...
Y-Yeah...
It's fine, isn't it?
Shiori-san!
Let's borrow some swimsuits from the Swimming Club.
This is kinda tight...
Really?
It's bulging...
Yeah...
Thanks for waiting!
Tada!
Ooh, Yukiko! Nice bikini!
I know, right? I found it!
Ooh, sweet!
That's nice too!
Wowza...
Yuka?
Yukiko-san made a big fuss about it...
She's really cute!
Your turn, Yuka-san!
Y-Yuka...
Feels so good... Right, Misuzu-senpai?
I suppose.
This is quite relaxing.
Totally!
I don't mind while bathing.
Yay!
It's kinda hot...
You can use that here, Takahisa-senpai?
See?
It's slightly salty.
You're right!
Does this have any special properties?
Maybe our skin becomes silky smooth!
Yup! And then your t*** and a** becomes bigger, causing the guys to become excited and f***** and g*** r*** us all at once!
Wanna try it?
On second thought, no talking!
It just occurred to me...
Yes?
Can't Kakeru-san use the Aeon's Eye to tell who the master of this world is?
Although just knowing who the master is won't really get us anywhere...
Just for now?
It may be gratifying.
What should I do?
Concentrate.
Concentrate?
You said that you could see through our clothes, right?
If you concentrate hard enough, maybe you can see the Voidstone Fragments within our bodies?
The fragment of the master of this world should be radiating energy right now.
I see. Okay, I'll try it!
Kakeru-kun...
Do your best!
Kakeru-kun!
Yuka-san?!
Wait, so this is Yuka's world?!
*Naked*
Don't look!
Perfect!
N-No!!
Y-Yuka?!
Her power's activated!
It's receded...
Yeah...
And who might you two be?
D-Don't tell me...
Kakeru-senpai and... Takahisa-senpai...?
What the? Kakeru?!
T-Takahisa?!
So this is Yuka-san's distorted power...
Don't worry! You two are now drop-dead hotties!
N-No~!!
And so, the
two new ladies,
Kakeru-san &
Takahisa-san
And so, the
two new ladies,
Kakeru-san &
Takahisa-san
And so, the
two new ladies,
Kakeru-san &
Takahisa-san
And so, the
two new ladies,
Kakeru-san &
Takahisa-san
both lived happily ever after.
No good?
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
This episode
of "11eyes"
is fictional.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
Any relation
to real life
is quite possible.
...are you angry?
Calcium is good for your health.