The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
It'd be nice if the Crimson Night doesn't come today.
That's right.
But is it really all right for me to come with you?
It's fine. Saeko's payday is everyones' payday.
That's mean! But I'll come along since you said so.
Yeah! Eat up, eat up! Eat it all up!
It's been so long since I've had grilled meat!
Hey, Saeko!
Let's go.
S-Sae...ko...
S-Saeko...
Saeko...
Saeko!!
Saeko!
Get yourself together!
Please...
Hey...
Say something, Saeko...
Saeko...
The Broken Bonds
I see it!
Shiori-san, who are you? Are you one of the black knights?
They said it's enough.
I have tested you.
You are slowly...
No... rapidly growing.
You are the one who bears our hope.
Hope?
You're dead!!
Good.
I'll shred all of your bonds into pieces!
Where in the world did Yukiko go?
She's such a handful.
At that time...
Invidia came prepared to blow herself up.
Y-You all should die...
I-It disappeared... My powers of destruction...
Why?
The enemy is willing to die to kill us.
Our unity is being put to the test.
If we don't cooperate now, we will die.
A fire?
Yukiko...
Yukiko!
Misuzu-senpai!
We were looking for you. Where were you?
Your clothes... What happened?
Die!!
You have awoken your power.
Please defeat the demons with that power.
Defeat...
...the demons?
The one who awoke the demons is you.
Also, the only one who can defeat the demons is you.
What are you talking about, Shiori-san?
Me, defeat them?
I was careless.
This mansion is already...
What's that!?
They're coming.
You're...
Superbia!
Master of the Aeon's Eye...
This isn't the Crimson Night.
Why are you here?
If we take lives, then we can also live between both worlds.
That's all there is to it.
Sensei was killed?
Y-Yes.
Ridiculous.
I can't believe something like that!
Unfortunately, it's the truth.
How is that possible?
We're not even in the Crimson Night...
How could Superbia have...
Senpai. You should accept what has happened and promptly assess the situation.
You're right.
Takahisa-senpai has lost himself to his own anger and sadness.
We have to hurry up, defeat Superbia and stop Takahisa.
Is that Kusukabe girl one of you?
What?
I'll just have to make you bring her out, then!
This is...
Superbia.
She's at my home.
There's no mistaking this enormous energy.
Then who is Takahisa-senpai fighting against?
Yukiko, I'm gonna leave Takahisa to you.
Kukuri and I will go to Superbia.
Can you do that?
Yes.
For friends and for tomorrow!
We're going back.
I'll go on ahead!
Something's strange.
What is this uneasiness?
Kakeru!
Misuzu-senpai!
So you've come.
Kashagiri Hiromitsu and Kannagiri Nagamitsu...
The Kusakabe clan must have fallen far to have entrusted them to you.
Kakeru, this person has incredible skill.
Back me up.
Okay!
Master of the Aeon's Eye,
I have prepared a different oppenent for you.
That's...
They're the Black Knights we defeated.
Kakeru!
Superbia...
No...
Kusukabe Misao !
Is it you, Misao?
Why?
Why would Kusakabe's greatest Onmyouji become a Black Knight?
In order to fight against ruin.
Ruin?
And also...
In order to protect Avaritia-sama!
Misao Kusukabe...
She truly is a legendary warrior.
I commend you for instantly knowing to step back from realizing the difference in our powers.
Also, for changing your strategy.
If you're prepared to strike me down,
you can't afford to make a single mistake.
I dedicate this life of mine for my friends and for tomorrow!
Why do you exist?
Such tremendous energy...
I can't move.
Kakeru has his hands full.
Why hasn't Kukuri come?
Yukiko hasn't returned yet?
Mama!
Takahisa-senpai!
Saeko had...
Saiko had raised me up until today.
She raised me, who was thrown away because of these powers!
I'm a hopeless guy.
If Saeko isn't around, I'll go insane!
Now you've done it, you bitch!
Takahisa-senpai!
Oh, it's you.
Please stop!
That's not a Black Knight. It's an illusion!
I suppose.
But I...
...can't stop this...
My parents, and my own horrific destructive impulses...
This demonic rampaging fire...
Yukiko...
I'm done for.
Sooner or later, I'm gonna lose control of myself...
Stop me...
For our friends and for tomorrow.
Stop it, Takahisa-senpai.
If you take me out...
I'll be satisfied!
The Crimson Night...
Two magic circles at once?
Yuka-san?
Yuka-san.
Shiori-chan...
What are you doing?
I'm waiting for Kakeru-kun.
He told me to stay here.
He's outside fighting with the Black Knights.
Kakeru-kun is?
I won't let you go.
Move it!
Move it, Shiori-chan!
If you are going to interfere with his growth, I will put you to sleep.
I'm going to protect Kakeru-kun!
I have to help Kakeru-kun!
The way he is right now, he is able to protect himself.
There's no way he can lose against those puppets.
Don't worry.
Really?
Yes.
Kakeru-kun is all right?
Then it's fine even if I don't go.
But I can't guarantee that everyone else is fine...
It's all right. As long as Kakeru-kun is fine.
Hey, Shiori-chan. Won't you have a cup of tea?
I'll go pour some!
It's useless. I can see through your attacks!
This is...
So that's how it is.
This is bad. It's going to become dangerous if she keeps wearing me down like this.
You know, Kakeru-kun and I were raised in the same facility.
Kakeru-kun has been so kind to me ever since.
He was always by side, protecting me...
I was then taken in by my current parents.
Kakeru started to live alone and joined the same high school as mine.
Kakeru-kun and I have always been together.
Always. Now and forever.
I really love how fairy-tales end.
"And so the two of them lived happily ever after."
Misuzu-senpai is...
You're only this strong?
I did expect a bit more out of you.
I see the end of the Kusakabe discipline coming near.
I just need one moment.
If I can find an opening for just one moment...
I ask for your protection and for the destruction of my enemies.
I call upon the god of fire and the flaming chariots to send my enemies into the depths of Hell!
I shall put everything into this attack.
Katentsuishou!
The Kashagiri is...
Damn you!
Playtime ends now.
Senpai!
Misuzu-senpai!
Just die!
Kakeru...
You drank the blood of Kusakabe, didn't you?
Let's leave it at this for the night.
However, as for "friends and for tomorrow"... I have destroyed all of it.
What?
Senpai?
Misuzu-senpai?
The Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum detected an evil disturbance and dispatched me here to Emegaoka.
So what's the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum?
It was made in order to seal the calamity that will bring absolute destruction to the world.
The world's greatest magical organization.
Magical organization?
Then you're a magician?
I'm not the only one.
They are also.
Who are you talking about?
The Black Knights, too?
They're not ordinary magicians, either.
They are disciples that have once been dispatched by the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum.
They are the ones that fought to bring an end to the demons.
Wait a second!
So are you saying that the Black Knights are actually fighting for justice?
No way...
It seems Misuzu-san is more familiar with Superbia, though.
We are worlds apart.
I'm not even a match for Kusakabe Misao .
It's useless...
I'm already...
Misuzu-senpai...
What's wrong, Yukiko?
I killed him...
I killed Takahisa-senpai...
I killed him with these hands...
Takahisa... died?
"For friends and for tomorrow"...
I have destroyed all of it.
Next episode: The Awakening of a Witch
Do you think there's an answer at the end of the nightmare?
Next Time
The Awakening of a Witch