The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
Yuka...
No way...
I'll save you.
We have failed...
How could we have let those damned fragments do this...
Ahh, the powers of darkness are embracing me...
It feels very nostalgic.
Liselotte Wreckmeister...
Oh, it's you?
So you went so far as to discard your original body to seal me away.
Such an evil aura... My body is warning me to run away...
So this is the Witch of Babylon...
Yuka... What have you done...
Good for you!
The Choice Called Ruin
Very well.
I shall grant...
...your wish!
Yuka!!
A Voidstone Fragment!
Yuka!
Yuka, open your eyes!
No way...
This can't be happening...
You've gotta be kidding me!
Yuka...
YUKA!!
Master of the Aeon's Eye...
Entrust your powers to me.
You shall become the one who brought ruin to this world.
Silence!
We shall crush all of your malicious desires to dust!
We cannot afford to give her more power!
Begone!
Huh? What's happening?
That black knight did this in order not to give Liselotte any more fragments or the Aeon's Eye.
Shiori's not here!
You bitch...
Bring us back! Bring us back to the Crimson Night where Yuka is!
This is...
Yuka! Yuka!!
Calm down, Kakeru!
But... But Yuka is...!
She may still be alive.
As a fellow member of the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum, I shall fight alongside you.
What?
Very well.
If your fragment comes too close to falling in Liselotte's hands, however...
I will end my own life.
Hmph. As you wish.
It is useless. Once the Descent to Hell begins, your lives will all be but forfeit.
Yuka's artificial world...
That's right. Seven Voidstone Fragments were dispersed to seven parallel worlds,
but once the black moon made its appearance, all the fragments gathered to one.
If that world still exists...
So Yuka's still alive!
Takahisa's rampage occurred in Yuka's world.
But that's not decisive proof...
I'll check whether or not Yuka exists in this world!
What're you talking about, Kakeru?
Well, Tadashi? Kaori?
Well, uh, about that... Right?
Answer me! Yuka... Do you know Minase Yuka?
We told you already over the phone, didn't we?
Of course we do. She's our friend.
Actually, she's more your beloved honey toast than a friend.
Your dear little piggy!
You meant "sweet honey", right?
And it's "little kitty".
Misuzu-senpai, this really is Yuka's world!
Um, I'm not following you on this...
Kakeru, did you hit your head somewhere or eat something bad?
She's alive...
Yuka is alive!
I hope that she is.
It's Kakeru's wish, after all...
Georgius...
The strongest land dragon with the power to inflict absolute terror upon its victims.
I will obliterate the Descent to Hell...
...and you, the Witch of Babylon, with it!
You shall perish!
Fools! The ones who will perish shall be you!
Abandon
all
hope,
ye
who
enter
here
Misuzu-senpai...
Is there nothing we can do?
Can we do nothing but wait?
Liselotte has yet to collect all the Voidstone Fragments.
Also...
There are fragments that have already been destroyed.
That's right! Liselotte's power is not as it was 64 years ago with her battle against the black knights!
That means we can win!
I wonder. Few of those black knights actually remain.
And that is all our fault.
We've no choice but to pray for their victory.
The two remaining black knights and Shiori would be fighting her in the Crimson Night right about now, right?
What only Kakeru and I can do now...
Your Voidstone Fragment... is mine!
This is my final battle.
Abraxus...
The guardian angel of Satsuki Kukuri...
...the one who took her own life seven years ago.
It's useless.
No matter how many weaklings you call on,
your destruction is still guaranteed.
Writhe and struggle in your hatred and lost wishes... and then die in the depths of despair!
Yuka's world still exists.
I want to believe that that's the proof Yuka still lives.
This black moon is the gate of darkness that's threatening to swallow everything...
I want to fight as well.
I want to go the Crimson Night and fight!
Kakeru. The next time we are called to the Crimson Night,
it means that Shiori and the black knights have failed, and Liselotte is trying to get her hands on you.
Liselotte is after me?
She cannot perform the Descent to Hell without all
seven fragments. She requires the Aeon's Eye now.
When that time comes, then the two of us must somehow overcome her.
However, neither of us has the power to do that.
Such futile attempts!
You are not from the Holy Ministry of the Index Librorum Prohibitorum, are you?
Avaritia-sama, deliver her judgment!
Forgive me, Superbia!
We can't win against Liselotte.
There is one way.
A way to rapidly increase our powers.
What is it?
Please tell me!
I'll do anything!
It...
It is performed by bonding a man and a woman who both have Kusakabe blood running in their veins.
Bonding...?
Intercourse.
Sexual intercourse.
That's just...
I don't mind.
But...!
Kakeru, I understand just how much you value Yuka.
I know that Yuka's existence is what fills your heart.
Just think of it as saving Yuka.
The next time we fight to protect this world, I shall probably die as your shield.
If that must be so...
I wish you to take me as a woman who longs for her loved one's hand.
Kakeru...
I love you.
This is a ceremony.
A ceremony that will strengthen us and enable us to fight.
I'm not betraying Yuka.
A pathway to the Crimson Night has been opened by our powers.
Senpai!
What a pitiful sight... It reminds me of my old self.
Who's there!?
You're...
Superbia!
No, Kusakabe Misao!
Over half a century ago, I too met Avaritia-sama across the distant seas...
...and fell in love.
My only repose in those days in the Kusakabe household were the times I spent with Avaritia-sama!
The battle... How did your battle go?
Avaritia-sama...
...was killed.
The one who wielded chains was obliterated, and the girl named Shiori took her own life.
Tachibana-senpai...
Shiori killed herself?
He's gone... My beloved Avaritia-sama is gone...
A world without him is no longer worth protecting.
In fact... let it be destroyed!
Let everything and everyone be obliterated!
Yuka... Where's Yuka!?
Kakeru-kun.
It's over, Kakeru-kun.
You don't have to worry any longer.
I ended it all for you.
Yuka... Is that you?
You're so funny!
Kakeru-kun... I love you!
Yuka...
Yuka!
Stop it!
Don't make me do this!!
Yu...ka...
Don't worry.
This girl lives inside me...
...as a Voidstone Fragment.
L-Liselotte!
Even my power is not enough to bring the world to ruin.
What I require... is the Aeon's Eye.
Welcome back, Verard. We meet again.
Why? Why must we hate each other?
Why must we kill each other?
Gone are the hearts of those who love.
Gone are the hearts of those who believe.
Such are the flaws of humans, Verard.
It is despairing... It is despicable.
I can no longer bear to gaze upon this world.
Liselotte...
Please be at ease.
A world like this does not deserve to exist.
Yes... I have no use for this world.
As long as I have you, I am content.
I shall now grant your wish.
K-Kakeru...
And so, they both lived happily ever after.
Hell no!
Next Time
Dawn of the Dark Night