Sorry... Kakeru.
This is the only way.
Onee-chan.
Yu... ka.
No!
This is...
Does this mean I can meet...
...that person?
Crimson Night
Incredible wind...
Man!
Yuka.
I came looking for you because you disappeared, Kakeru-kun.
Good thing you didn't return first.
What are you looking at?
The clouds?
The moon.
The moon? Where?
You're right.
It's pretty.
Yuka...
Seven years ago...
my older sister ended her own life.
Being brought up in an institution,
my sister was my only family.
That's why I couldn't completely accept what happened...
and closed my heart.
Only Yuka, who was from the same institution,
had always smiled at me.
She had stayed close, and laughed for me.
If Yuka weren't here, I wonder how I would've turned out.
What's wrong, Kakeru-kun?
No, it's nothing.
Shall we return?
Even so... I...
Kakeru!
Yuka!
Kaori-chan!
Tadashi-kun!
It looks like you found Kakeru-kun.
Yeah, he was looking at the moon on the roof.
The moon?
You two were up on the roof alone this whole time?
Well... yeah.
What were you doing?
What do you mean? Nothing much.
Some dazzling event had occured, right, Kakeru-kun?
You have to send me a picture mail! Picture mail!
What kind of weird delusions are you having, you idiot.
Tadashi-kun! Kaori-chan, you're going overboard.
It looks like you've made me get serious.
You have woken up the real me inside of me.
You can't stop me now.
Don't say "you"!
S-Strong...
Dang you! You must be the legendary...!
Though I don't talk much, if at all, with anyone other than Yuka, Tadashi and Kaori casually came up to me.
When I'm with the cheerful twosome, my feelings naturally become calm.
Sale?
Yeah, they're saying that today and tomorrow there's going to be an outlet sale at Ianith.
What kinds of outlets are at Ianith?
Lots of stuff.
Like western clothing or general goods-
Or indecent gravure photo shoots.
Go to hell, perverted Tadashi.
Hey, we're going right now, so you wanna come too?
Really? That sounds fun.
I'm fine.
I don't like crowds.
Go ahead, you don't need to mind me.
Sorry, I'll go next time.
Yuka was adopted by the Minase family the year she entered elementary school.
The married Minase couple, who had no children, warmly welcomed Yuka.
Well then, see you tomorrow.
Yeah.
See you.
Yuka!
On second thought, should we go?
Ianith.
Yup!
What is it?
Because I'm happy!
Yuka...
What... is this?
Kakeru-kun.
A black... moon....
Out of
Range
What's going on?
Kakeru-kun, what in the world's going on, hey!?
I also don't know what's happening.
No one's around.
Everyone's disappeared somewhere.
Father! Mother!
They're not here.
Yuka!
Something's there.
Let's go!
Where are we going?
That's right, let's go to school.
School?
There might be a chance someone is there.
What is... that?
Kakeru-kun!
We're running away!
We're... back?
Are you all right, Kakeru-kun?
Yuka...
You saw a bad dream, didn't you?
Yeah, but why are you...
When I came to pick you up, your door was open.
I thought something happened and I panicked.
I see.
When we came back yesterday, I was a bit dazed.
What about you, are you okay?
I couldn't sleep last night.
I see.
I was too scared to close my eyes... so scared.
Yeah, I was too.
I couldn't sleep either.
You were just sleeping, soundly.
Well, if you jump to conclusions...
You do remember, right?
Please wait.
Yuka?
Will it happen again?
That... Crimson Night.
Hey!
Good morning!
What is this, what is this?
Walking to school together like a date?
Don't say unnecessary things.
I'll protect you.
If anything happens again, I will protect you, Yuka.
So don't worry.
Kakeru-kun...
I'm happy...
I'm so happy...
I-Idiot!
Don't cry in a place like this.
People will misunderstand.
Y-You made her cry!
You made a girl cry in the morning.
See?
Sorry.
Let's go in.
Yeah.
Everyone, let me introduce a transfer student.
Shiori Momono
17 July
Duty
Teruna
Yatsuki
This is Shiori Momono-san.
C-Cute! Moe!
Momono-san came back to Japan from Italy.
Italy? Cool!
Now then, Momono-san, please introduce yourself.
There is no need.
Huh?
Shiori Momono
17 July
Duty
Teruna
Yatsuki
There is no need.
Hey, what's your hobby?
Where's your house at?
Are you interested in Kuino Shirohara?
Yeah, yeah, yeah!
Ask your questions in order.
Let's see. Now first, what's your three sizes-
Die!
I don't have any interest in you all.
So don't interfere with me.
What is it?
Um...
Yuka!?
Yuka!
Kakeru-kun...
I can walk now.
No you can't.
It's because I'm lacking sleep.
I'm all right.
It's embarrassing.
Infirmary
Move it.
You're in the way.
Can't you see? I've got a sick person!
Sick person?
Hey!
That guy...
What's wrong?
Oh, playing princess?
No... it's... Sorry.
It's just anemia, don't worry.
Is that so? Then, I'll go back.
Thank you, Kakeru-kun.
Rest a bit.
You are Satsuki, right?
Yes.
What happened to that eye?
It's all right if you don't want to say anything.
I had it since birth.
Is that right?
Excuse me.
Minase...
Kakeru-kun can't see through his right eye.
Because of that, his irises have a different color so he wears the eye patch.
That's not it.
Is he... your boyfriend?
S-Sensei!
Oh I see. It's still in that stage.
That was...
So, did you get some sleep?
Yeah, so I'm all right.
Sorry, for making you worry.
If it's not too hard on your body, shall we go?
Eh?
Ianith. We couldn't go yesterday, right?
The outlet sale is until today.
Kakeru-kun...
Yup!
Oh right. Mother and Father said for you to come over sometime and eat.
Yeah, I should.
You want to come over today when we return?
Nah, I'll come over another day.
That aside, you always carry that but... what is it?
Penzo-san!
Penzo... san?
Penzo-san is incredible, you know.
See?
Y-Yeah, incredible.
I know right?
Let's... not go here.
Yeah.
That was fun.
Is it really all right not having bought anything?
It's okay. If I'm with you, it's fun just looking around.
It was a good thing we came.
It's not like the shock and insecurity from yesterday has worn off...
...but this smile isn't a lie.
Hey, Kakeru-kun.
Hmm?
Shall we... do that?
Okay.
Y-Yuka?
Okay!
Please.
Yeah.
Whatever that thing was doesn't matter.
I don't want Yuka to have painful thoughts anymore.
As long as it doesn't happen again, everything's fine.
It's quiet, isn't it?
Yeah.
It'd be nice if it were always like this, right?
Kakeru... kun?
Kukuri-san!
Kakeru-kun.
What the heck is going on?
Why has Nee-san...
Kakeru-kun!
It's all right.
That boy is...
Yuka!
Next time:
The Crystal Maiden.
At the end of the nightmare...
...is there an answer?
Next Time
The Crystal Maiden