The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
I want to protect Yuka.
I want to protect her.
Kakeru-kun!
We've got trouble! Yuka is...
Yuka!
For Friends and Tomorrow
Anemia?
Yup, it's just anemia.
Sorry, even though I said I was all right, Kaori-chan said...
That's cause she said that you collapsed in the classroom.
Yes, but it's nothing to worry about.
I'll be fine if I just lie down for a bit.
More importantly, I'm worried about you.
I'm fine.
The sketchbook...
We'll find out the meaning of that sooner or later.
There's no use worrying about it.
You aren't worried about it?
Yeah!
Please don't lie to me.
Yuka...
Kakeru-kun...
It's nice that you two get along well.
Ah... no... well...
This is so cheesy that I can't stand listening to it.
He's not cute at all, right?
That guy.
S-Sorry, I couldn't see in front of me.
Takahisa-senpai!
I'll be taking this.
U-Um...
Are you really all right now?
Yeah, I'm fine now.
Minase.
Yes, Saiko-sensei?
You said sleep deprivation, but what's the cause?
Well, whatever. You're at that age where a lot of things happen, after all.
It's not good unless you sleep properly, though.
Yes.
Let's see... If you can't seem to sleep again, try having a lullaby sung to you.
A lullaby?
Right, Satsuki?
Y-You're talking about me?
Even through the phone is fine, so just sing for her.
Well, but me? Singing a lullaby?
It may be embarrassing at first but you'll get used to it.
I was also like that.
You sang lullabies, too?
Oh, is that strange?
Well, because...
Who did you sing to?
Who, you say? To my child.
Your child?!
Sensei, you have children?!
You two have seen him already.
Remember? That un-cute delinquent.
Oba-chan, the usual.
What are you surprised about?
Well, because...
Ah, it doesn't all add up?
Uh-huh.
Yeah.
Well, that's natural. He's not my real son, after all.
If there was a title, I'd be something like a "childhood parent."
Childhood...?
A long time ago, I was...
Something of a mischievous motorcycle enthusiast.
A mischievous motorcycle enthusiast?
Ah, you mean "ladies"?
Well, to be blunt, yes...
So that night, a lot of things had happened, so I was being chased by the police, and...
Wha-?
A kid?
They're what you'd call street children.
He was trying to live on in his own childish way.
A kid is still a kid, though.
At that moment, I suddenly thought, "Who's going to protect this kid?"
Well, that's the result of my youth. Right now I regret picking him up.
Street children...
He's the same as us who were raised at an orphanage.
Yeah...
I see... you two, too...
All right then, we'll be leaving.
Make sure you get him to sing a lullaby for you.
Yes!
Hey, Yuka!
You'll sing for me, right, Kakeru-kun?
Well, that's...
Wait, wait, wait!
WAIT!!
Awesome!
You don't have to be scared anymore, cute little lost kitty!
Tadashi, it's dangerous if you let your guard down.
See? Geez, right after I said it.
Careful, the kitty's dangerous!
Yo.
It disappeared...
It disappeared?
What did?
It's a secret to ordinary people.
Who's going to protect this kid?
Kusakabe-senpai!
Kakeru-kun!
Hey, good timing.
After school again today... please!
Swordsmanship? Today, I'll introduce you to someone before that.
A person? Ah, you did say that before...
The girl is finally prepared to meet you all.
Kakeru-kun, practice comes after that.
All right then, after school... at the Modern Society Studies Club.
Thanks for coming!
W-Why?
Sorry for the late notice!
Takahisa-senpai has became a "Modern Society Studies" member as of today!
No I haven't. I only came cause you said it's all-you-can-eat snacks.
Handkerchief, handkerchief, handkerchief!
Are you all right?
Yeah.
Hold it!
Kakeru-kun.
Sorry, I'm late.
Did something happen here?
Nothing, really.
Ahh, oh no!
Everyone, let me introduce her. She's Tachibana Kukuri-kun from Class 3-B.
K-Kukuri-san...?!
N-Nee-san?
I see. Just like your older sister...
Yes.
We'd seen her a few times, and each time it made my heart skip a beat. She looked very similar.
Kukuri-kun can't speak.
Her ears are fine so she can understand what you say.
When she's in a conversation, she'll need to write, though.
I think everyone will get used to it soon.
So that's how it is. I understand!
I'm Hirohara Yukiko. My pleasure!
That's an impressively nice pair you have there, senpai.
Yu-Yukiko-chan!
Ah, that's right.
Faad sehteio fresce en tora!
Thai: เพื่อผองเพื่อนและวันพรุ่งนี้ - lit. "To his friends, and tomorrow"
Surprised?
Well, of course we'd be. What was that just now?
I said, "Faad sehteio fresce en tora."
A foreign language?
It's the language of the country, Dransvania, I was born in.
It means, "for friends and tomorrow."
What do you think?
Well, what are you asking...?
It's our secret password.
Password?
We use it when we want to say "don't give up!"
I think it would be nice to have it...
I see. It's not bad.
Right? "For friends and tomorrow."
Yeah, it's good. Really good!
Right, right?
Kukuri-senpai, what do you think?
Thank you very much!
You can't do much about Yukiko-kun.
"For friends and tomorrow."
Kakeru-kun?
Oh, do you like it too?
All right, let's all say it together. Got it?
Ready, set...
Ridiculous.
What do you mean, a "secret password"?
It's not like you're a kid.
Geez, Takahisa-senpai is just embarrassed.
I'll bring him back here.
Leave him alone.
Someone like him is...
Kakeru-kun.
That guy isn't one of us.
Isn't that great?
Kukuri-san... It's surprising that she had the same name but also a relief that she's someone else.
Yeah...
What's on your mind?
"For friends and tomorrow"...
Friends and tomorrow... I've never thought about those things before.
It was surprising.
Kakeru-kun...
It's a great expression. "For friends and tomorrow."
It's been a while...
Huh?
I'm kind of happy that I got to see you smile.
Yuka...
What the...?
Ouch...
What is that?
A wall?
Only me?
Where's Kukuri-san?
Now that you mention it... maybe in the bathroom?
I'll go take a look.
Kusakabe-senpai.
Sword practice... please.
Kakeru-kun, it's already late today, so...
Step back.
You're going to do it here?
Stop right there!
Look at your feet.
When did you...
If you stepped on that, you'd slip.
Once you lose your footing, it's over in one hit.
You're blindly trying to go up to your opponents.
Not only now. It's ever since the first time.
You want to protect Yuka-kun.
That feeling rises first, so you turn a blind eye to everything else.
The first thing to do is keep your composure.
Everything starts from there.
For those that are ruled by feelings, there is no chance of winning.
Kakeru-kun...
All right, let's go home.
So they've come...!
Wipe out the "fragments"!
Run outside!
Yes.
Damned "fragments"... I'll cut you to pieces!
Go!
All right!
Where did Kukuri-senpai go?
I wonder if she's all right...
Takahisa-senpai!
They should at least knock if they're opening the door, shouldn't they?
This is the womens' bathroom, you know.
Yeah...
We're almost there!
You guys can't beat me.
Kakeru-kun!
You can't even make a single scratch.
Watch the end of whom you wanted to protect...
...and thus feel your powerlessness.
N-no... don't come any closer!
No!
Kakeru-kun...
It seems like you want to die first, no matter what.
Well then let me grant your wish!
There's too much of a gap in our power.
Attacking first won't help.
I'll only lose... but... what can I do?!
That's...
Kogarasumaru...
First thing to do is keep your composure.
For those that are ruled by feelings, there is no chance of winning.
That's right... I can't rush things...
I have to be calm.
What is it, you good-for-nothing?
Bring it on.
Are you so scared that you've gone insane?
Kakeru-kun?
Change feelings into strength. Just think about that.
Change feelings... into strength.
I will protect Yuka.
Die!
What? You dodged it?
What was that now?
I see... So that's how it is!
You eye is... don't tell me...!
No... it can't be possible.
There's no way a quiet kid like this can awaken!
I see it.
My armor... impossible!
This time it's Ira...
He's awakened.
What?
Lisette, what did you say?
That guy...
K-Kakeru-kun?
Kakeru-kun!
Kakeru-kun...?
What's wrong? Hey, Kakeru-kun!
KAKERU-KUN!!
So you've finally awakened.
Shudder in fear... of thy power.
That eye shall grant you everything and strip away everything.
The world you love... the people you love...
You are...
My name is Verard, king of the fallen country.
The one chosen by the Aeon's Eye.
Next time: The Upset Hearts
LIFE
Is there an answer at the end of the nightmare?
Next Time
The Upset Hearts