The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
Let's go to the places where Yuka might have gone.
Yes.
You might be too late already.
Takahisa-senpai!
You're beat up everywhere!
She was a surprisingly tough enemy.
She got away, though.
What do you mean by too late?
That's Yuka-san's...
Where did you see that?
Where did you see that thing?
In the infirmary.
Senpai!
It was quite a mess... that infirmary.
Don't tell me...
Kakeru-kun is...
Kakeru-kun is changing.
Sorry.
Kakeru-kun is... My Kakeru-kun is...
No...
No!! I don't want that!!
A Twisted Awakening
Infirmary
The infirmary's been obliterated...
Yuka... Yuka!
Calm down, Kakeru!
It's all right, Senpai. Yuka-san isn't here.
There is no scent of blood.
We can't say for sure that she's safe, but it seems she at least escaped.
She couldn't have gone that far in this amount of time.
Let's split up and search for her.
It's dangerous but I guess there's no choice.
Yukiko. Kukuri. We'll search door to door around the school.
Understood.
Kakeru and Takahisa are extremely exhausted.
While you wait until you recover fully, search within the school.
No, me too...
Hey, hey.
Don't go telling us what to do.
If you find Yuka, come back to school right away and group up with Kakeru and Takahisa.
Once Takahisa shoots off a pillar of fire as a signal, we all return to the school.
You'll do at least that, right?
Aye, aye, Captain.
All right, Kakeru?
Yes!
All right, let's go!
Yes! For friends and tomorrow!
For friends and tomorrow!
Yuka-san! Yuka-san!
Yuka! Yuka!
Next is the gymnasium!
Hey!
You okay?
It's my fault. If only I hadn't left Yuka all alone...
Yuka...
Sorry.
Yuka!
Stay safe, Yuka.
What's so funny?!
My bad, my bad. Don't get angry.
You sure can express your feelings about girls without being embarrassed, Kakeru.
What?
Nothing, really. I just wondered if I would become that stubborn if someone close to me disappeared.
Yukiko has the same scent as I do.
That's why it hurts to smile. I guess you'd call it karma.
Let's stop. If you knew what I'd done, I'm sure that even you would change.
I've been watching you all this time.
I know.
Tell me about it.
It's a secret! If you're too mindful of me, it'd just be awkward instead.
How pathetic of me... I worried too much.
These damn bugs.
Don't be eavesdropping on people's secret conversations!
Takahisa!
Let's go and search for your princess.
The black moon is...
...getting closer to the Earth...
Yuka-san! Oh lost little Yuka-san!
If you're there, please answer back in a loud voice!
Yuka―
This is...
I'm glad that you like it, Kakeru-kun.
I'll make you a bento tomorrow, too.
Yuka-san!
Hey, Kakeru-kun. Do you like me?
I love Kakeru-kun.
Yuka-san?
Kakeru-kun?
This is...?
That sly witch trying her futile attempts to escape while we're away.
Superbia.
Yes.
I shall leave the destruction of the fragments and the Aeon's Eye's wielder to you, Invidia, and Scholastica.
Understood, Avaritia-sama.
You heard that, Invidia?
An ugly defeat and that hideous burn...
Now you have only one other thing left to do!
Yuka-san, are you all right?
If we don't return quickly, everyone will worry.
Ah, that's right! I've got some good news. Kukuri-san took care of a Black Knight.
Kukuri-san's power was amazing.
Everyone is amazing, aren't they?
Yes?
Even though everyone has amazing powers and are risking their lives fighting, I'm the only one that's...
You don't have to worry about that!
Fighting doesn't fit you.
It's because I didn't have any powers that Kakeru-kun left me.
What are you talking about? Kakeru-senpai and you are passionately in love, aren't you?
He's only fighting because he wants to protect you.
You're loved, in a lot of different ways!
Why, you little...!
Yuka-san...
Maybe I'll tell you... about my past.
Up until a Japanese person picked me up,
I lived in the country of Drasvenia.
By the time I was old enough to be aware of things, the world was already hell itself.
A civil war to wash away blood with blood.
Everyone fought to hold what was precious to them amongst the mayhem and destruction.
Men, women, and children...
I have a immortal body. If I blow myself up or step on a mine, I still regenerate.
That's why I was used as a human weapon.
My family and friends died one after another.
That's why I killed and killed and continued to kill.
Only the phrase "For my friends and tomorrow" kept supporting me.
My personality and battle abilities were honed in that hell.
If they hadn't, I wouldn't have been able to protect my friends... and my future.
If I don't seal myself with my glasses, I become a really dangerous girl.
I don't want you to be like me, Yuka-san.
That's why it's better not to awaken your powers to fight.
I'm pretty sure Kakeru-senpai would like it that way, too.
Yukiko-chan!
Yuka-san...
Yukiko-chan, I'm all right. I'm all right now...
After all, I...
It's useless.
This isn't something you can do!
That is...
Tachibana Ophthalmology
W-What is this light?
Scholastica... You, who fought with your own brother Benedictus...
Your vessel you return to, Acedia, is no longer present.
Die at once.
Scholastica...
The Black Knights are...
What happened here?
It's you again? You're annoying!
Being mere "fragments"... the sin for hurting my pride and face... I'll have you pay with your lives.
Stop blabbing. I'll return those words right back at you!
...Which is what I'd love to say, but we're running out of gas here. What'll you do, Kakeru?
We've no choice but to fight, right?
Then I'll go first!
Kakeru!
Misuzu-senpai!
You saved us.
Here I come!
Your opponent is me!
Invidia, you may fight to your hearts content!
Hurry up and come back, Yukiko, Tachibana-senpai!
Where's she? Where'd she go?
Behind me, huh?
That weapon... It's one of the Kusakabe weapons, Kashagiri Hiromitsu, right?
What?
Your stance is the style of Kusakabe household.
So you're an Onmyouji of the Kusakabe family after all.
Why do you know such a thing?
To be able to fight a Kusakabe swordswoman... It seems fate is quite mischievous.
That's the Kusakabe dual wield balancing stance... Why do you... Don't tell me...
My eyes...
I-I'm at my limit, too...
The sin of being a fragment won't be lifted until your soul gets destroyed.
What an incredible blood lust. I can't move.
Who in the world are you?!
You're...
The end of time is near. You all shouldn't even exist!
Tachibana-senpai!
You're late, Yukiko!
I-It can't be. There's no way it could be...
It looks like you're not in the position to be fighting.
My name is Superbia. I shall postpone this match for later.
I'll leave the rest to you, Invidia.
Kakeru.
Misuzu-senpai.
What is this?
Is it a barrier to seal us in here?
A barrier?
Y-You all should die...
She plans on self-destructing!
You can't be serious!
We've got to run!
Holder of Aeon's Eye and you "fragments"... I'll take you all down with me!
Stop it!!
Don't touch Kakeru-kun!!
That's...
Isn't that Yuka?
What?
I-It disappeared... My powers of destruction...
Why?
Yuka...
What happened? What did Yuka do?
Mostly likely, the light she released negated our powers.
Powers?
Yuka... has awakened...
Yuka is amazing...
It's amazing... but it's also a dangerous power.
Dangerous?
Didn't you see? Not only the enemy's, but our powers get negated, too.
It's all right, Kakeru-kun. I'm here for you.
I'll protect you.
So please... lay your eyes.... only on me...
Yuka!
He was usurped?
No way... it can't be. Verard is...
I won't allow it. I definitely won't allow it.
I'll destroy it... this filthy world.
That's the wish of Verard and I, Liselotte!
Yuka... I didn't want Yuka to awaken.
I didn't want to drag her into the fight.
Tachibana-senpai...
How is Yuka-san's condition?
The one who woke up the
demon is you.
Don't tell me... that's...
Next time: The Time of Disasters
Takahisa, we're going for barbecue!
We'll have Galbi, sirloin, and an extra big serving of savarin... Eat as much as you like!
TL NOTE: Galbi (갈비) is a Korean dish of grilled ribs marinated in soy sauce.
Next Time
The Time of Disasters