The Crimson Night --- it suddenly appears.
A reality yet not a reality, a shadow world with a different space-time.
The young men and women who fall there are called “fragments,” and are assaulted by grotesque black knights.
Why is it them, what exactly is occurring-
At the end of the nightmare, is there an answer?
Even though his powers finally awakened...
It's because he tried using it without knowing how.
How stupid can he be?
How can you say something like that?! Kakeru-kun did it to save me―
Kakeru-kun!
Well, shouldn't we take him to the hospital...?
Every nerve in his body is damaged. He's lucky to be alive.
Even if we were to carry him to the hospital, they wouldn't be able to offer any cure.
Then Kakeru-senpai is...?
That's why I brought him here.
I will heal him.
The Upset Hearts
He'll be all right, Yuka-san. Let's believe in Misuzu-san!
Life
Here goes...
If only I could stand by his side...
Kakeru-kun...
Kukuri-san! Thank goodness! You were safe!
Rin, Pyou, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen.
TL Note: These are the Kuji-in (九字印), "Nine Hand Seals," which are a specialized form of Buddhist meditation.
In order: 「臨 rin」 (to confront), 「兵 pyou」 (soldier), 「闘 tou」 (to fight), 「者 sha」 (person),
Rin, Pyou, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen.
「皆　kai」 (everyone), 「陣 jin」 (battle formation), 「列 retsu」 (rank/file), 「在 zai」 (existence), 「前　zen」 (forward).
This chant symbolizes all forces against evil and was often used to conquer troublesome situations.
Here you go.
Thanks, Yukiko-chan.
It'll calm you down.
It's my fault.
There has to be some kind of power in me, too, but if only I had awakened it, Kakeru-kun wouldn't have gone through that.
Wait, what are you talking about? This isn't your fault, Yuka-san!
No... I'm to blame.
Where are you going?
To where Kakeru-kun is.
Misuzu-san said that you can't go in there.
I know. I won't go inside.
That's not good...
Rin, Pyou, Tou, Sha, Kai, Jin, Retsu, Zai, Zen.
Kakeru-kun...
Life
Hang in there.
Is it painful?
That is the power you seek. It is the power of Aeon's Eye.
Aeon's... Eye?
If you discard your life, you'll be at ease.
That just means I'll return to my rest.
However, if you wish to continue seeking this power, then live on.
I won't die. I can't die yet.
Can't die?
I will protect Yuka! I will... protect...
To protect the ones you love... Are you saying that you can protect them?
I will protect them!
You can taste the despair, right?
You shall feel loss beyond comparison, and also come to know just how powerless you are.
Just as I have.
It's morning?
W-What the-
Just great...
I wonder if it's over yet...
Just a peek...
A-Are you all right?
Yeah, sorry.
With your powers of Onmyou, you...
Does anything hurt?
I'm fine.
I see. That's good.
Senpai!
I'm all right.
Sorry to put you through this.
All I did was boost your own regenerative ability.
You were healed by your own life powers.
It's impressive that you were able to recover that much.
I... won't die. I can't die yet.
I will protect Yuka!
I'm gonna go wash up. When I come back, tell me about that eye.
Sure.
Good mornin'... I fell asleep.
Eh? What is it?
There's nothing here...
Your bed head is funny.
Bed head?
That's awesome!
I see, so you communicate with that, eh?
Yes ♡
Ah, Misuzu-san! Good morning! Is it over now?
Yeah.
Kakeru-senpai is okay now, right?
Yeah, he's all right now.
You're great, Misuzu-san!
No fondling.
By the way, did Kukuri-kun make the food?
Did you also bring some to that room earlier?
Kukuri-san communicates via the sketchbook.
Yeah, I know.
It was Yuka-san
Ah, now that you mention it, I did pass her in the hallway earlier.
I greeted her, but she didn't reply. She seemed to be in thought.
Yuka.
Morning.
What's wrong?
Nothing. That's great, it looks like you're healthy again.
Yeah, thanks to Misuzu-senpai.
That's great. It really is.
Yuka, what's wrong? Did something happen?
Nothing, really.
It's all right. It's not like that.
It's all right. I believe in Kakeru-kun, after all.
Kakeru-kun wouldn't do something like that...
No, it's true! There really was a cat with dog eyes!
I got it, I got it.
You don't believe me, do you? It's the truth!
It had eyes like this!
Are you ready?
Yes.
Good. Let's go.
I'm kinda happy to be able to go with everyone!
Again...
Yukiko-chan, look, she's troubled.
Really? You're happy, aren't you?
All right, let's get going.
Misuzu-senpai!
I'm all right.
Shouldn't you take a rest today?
I'll sleep in class. Don't worry, Kakeru.
Yuka... Yuka!
Is something wrong with Yuka-san?
Yuka...
Hey, Shiori-chan. Walking while reading a book is dangerous.
That's why you're here.
Eh?
Make sure you be my eyes and protect me.
Protect? In that case, instead of being your eyes, I'll come and hug you, Shiori-chi!
It's still too early in the morning to be saying stuff like that, idiot!
Sorry, Shiori-chan!
Your red nose is also cute.
Kaori-san, please give him a couple.
Yes, ma'am.
Is that all right?
Well, let's leave it at that this time.
Yuka...
There she goes...
She didn't have her bag, huh?
It's Kakeru.
Kakeru!
What's with him?
He didn't have his bag either, huh?
Seigan...?
That's what we call it in Onmyoudo.
It's possible to look into the future with it, but...
Its usage is hard. It's a cursed eye called "Jagan."
Kakeru-senpai has that eye.
Kakeru-kun called it the Aeon's Eye.
Eh? Aeon's Eye? Really?!
Do you know about it?
I heard about it when I was younger.
In the medieval ages, the king of the kingdom Drasvenia had Aeon's Eye.
And the name of that king?
I don't remember that much...
Verard?
Ah! That's it! I'm surprised you know, Misuzu-san!
It seems that he appeared in Kakeru's dream.
In his dream?
So how did that king die?
I heard that he got tricked by a witch and his country fell, so he took his own life.
Witch...
It can't be...
So... does that have anything to do with Yuka-san's behaviour?
No... That's an entirely different situation.
Different?
Yuka!
What's wrong? What happened?
It's nothing.
There's no way it can be nothing.
Tell me about it. Did I do something?
You said, "Misuzu-senpai."
You called Misuzu-san "Misuzu-senpai."
What's wrong with that?
Misuzu-san called you "Kakeru."
What are you talking about?
It's just strange! You were calling her "Kusakabe-senpai"!
And she was calling you "Kakeru-kun"!
Up until yesterday, anyways...
But that changed this morning.
Hey, Yuka. Get a grip on yourself!
What nonsense are you talking about?
I saw you two!
That's not it, Yuka. You're mistaken.
Misuzu-senpai and I aren't...
You said it again. You called her "Misuzu-senpai" again.
Yuka, can't you believe me?
Leave the city?
That's right. I thought about that.
During the Crimson Night, you can't see past the horizon, right?
If we left the city, we wouldn't have to go through the Crimson Night anymore... I think...
That's impossible.
Takahisa-senpai!
Impossible?
I already tried that. I couldn't leave.
What do you mean by "couldn't leave"?
There's a wall. There some kind of strange wall surrounding the city.
A wall?
What do you mean by "wall"? What're you talking about?
It's nothing to do with you.
I'll decide on that after I hear what it's about.
Stop fussing over me like some goddamn grandma!
You're coming with me, boy.
Hey... hold... on... let go...!
No excuses!
You're coming with me! Hurry up!
Wall, huh...
Kiss me.
Yuka...
Sorry.
I don't want to with these feelings.
I...
Yuka!
So they're here...
The Crimson Night...
I'll have you show me.
Leave it to me, Avaritia-sama.
Don't you dare touch my prey, Acedia.
My target is the holder of that eye.
Don't let your guard down, Acedia.
I'm different from Ira.
Yuka... Yuka, where are you?
Kakeru!
Senpai, Yuka's...!
Wasn't she with you?
Kukuri-san is here!
All right, let's look for Yuka.
Keep together, everyone!
Burn!
That's it! Keep bringing on the strongest you've got!
So we meet again.
What's this... A weak one showed up...
You'll pay for what you've done to my face.
I think I'm gonna have a barbecue with you today.
I won't kill you that simply. You will suffer as much as I have!
I guess it should be, "Nice to meet you."
Why do you call us "fragments"? Why attack us?
We have no reason to fight with you in this world!
Even if you don't have a reason, we do.
What do you mean by that?
I almost feel sorry for you for not knowing anything.
Then how about you tell us? Would it be inconvenient for you to do that?
Occasionally, being self-conscious of adversity can strengthen oneself,
which gives one the bothersome feeling of being responsible for everything.
In other words, if we know the truth, you guys won't be able to win?
I won't play along with your sly interrogations.
Let me tell you just one thing. Your existences themselves are a sin.
You speak as if you are the one that yields justice.
All of you must disappear.
For the future...
The future?
Kakeru, go! Leave this to me.
But Senpai, your body's still...!
You're going to protect Yuka, right?
Yukiko and Kukuri, too!
Yes!
You won't escape, holder of Aeon's Eye.
Black Tortoise Genbu, with the power of the sixtieth sexagenary cycle, dispatch my foe!
Kyuukyuunyoritsuryou!
急急如律令: A spell used by Esoteric Buddhists, and also in Shugendou. Roughly means "Bend thy will to the law immediately."
Don't get in my way, you damn fragment!
Breath of the Water Dragon!
Misuzu-senpai!
That's right. Show me just what you can do.
Don't do it, Kakeru. You aren't ready to use it yet!
If you fight, this time your body will...
My body's screaming out, but I don't have a choice but to do it!
What's wrong? Are you done already?
Black Knight!
Pesky creature!
Damn you...
How the...
Abraxus, huh?
That was amazing, Kukuri-san!
So that was Kukuri's power...
Scholastica ran away?
Bonds, huh...
That power is like a diamond, hard yet easily shattered.
Let's go to the places where Yuka might have gone.
Yes.
You might be too late already.
Takahisa-senpai!
You're beat up everywhere!
She was a surprisingly tough enemy.
She got away, though.
What do you mean by too late?
That's Yuka-san's...
Where did you see that?
Where did you see that thing?
In the infirmary.
Senpai!
It was quite a mess... that infirmary.
Don't tell me...
Yuka...
Yuka!!
Next time: A Twisted Awakening
We can only hope for an answer at the end of the nightmare.
Next Time
A Twisted Awakening